<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ModOps>
  <!-- START William Henry Pilkington, Glass safety expert  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000002</GUID>
      <Text>William Henry Pilkington, Glass safety expert</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000003</GUID>
      <Text>Also known as "Harry". He made his career optimizing the glass making process and specialized in safety glass. No stronger glass can be found.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END William Henry Pilkington, Glass safety expert  -->
  <!-- START Gretl Brown, Mother of the Forests  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000004</GUID>
      <Text>Gretl Brown, Mother of the Forests</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000005</GUID>
      <Text>Mother of Ursula and Greta. Wife of Carsten Green. Loves to work together with Ursula inside the forests and has a passion for wild berries and making jam. The fruits she uses for her jams are from the forests and she uses small colonies of her own bees to help the forest bloom.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Gretl Brown, Mother of the Forests  -->
  <!-- START Carsten Green, Father of the Arctic Forests  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000006</GUID>
      <Text>Carsten Green, Father of the Arctic Forests</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000007</GUID>
      <Text>Father of Ursula and Greta. Husband of Gretl Brown. Loves to work together with Greta inside the cold woods of the Arctic. He loves animals and huskies in particular. He has a passion of domesticating wild huskies.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Carsten Green, Father of the Arctic Forests  -->
  <!-- START Greta Green, Guardian of the Arctic Forests  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000008</GUID>
      <Text>Greta Green, Guardian of the Arctic Forests</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000009</GUID>
      <Text>Following in her father's footsteps, Greta decided to show her love for the woods in the cold Arctic. Together with her father she spends her days conserving the woods of the Arctic. She fell in love with one of the local hunters. Nukilik Takirak. She brews her own strong drinks to keep warm.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Greta Green, Guardian of the Arctic Forests  -->
  <!-- START Nukilik Takirak, The strongest hunter  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000010</GUID>
      <Text>Nukilik Takirak, The strongest hunter</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000011</GUID>
      <Text>Being the strongest hunter of his tribe, Nukilik was always looking for more in life. When people from other regions came to the Arctic he met Greta Green and fell in love with her. She made his life whole and they shared their love for the forests.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Nukilik Takirak, The strongest hunter  -->
  <!-- START Brandon Heat, The perfectionist charcoal burner  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000012</GUID>
      <Text>Brandon Heat, The perfectionist charcoal burner</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000013</GUID>
      <Text>Brandon perfected the art of wood burning for charcoal in the Arctic. He came to the Arctic together with his sister Jenny. Apart from creating a huge amount of charcoal with some extra help he found ways to extract more resources from the conifers of the Arctic and drains resin from them.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Brandon Heat, The perfectionist charcoal burner  -->
  <!-- START Arnakuagsak Takirak, Huntress of the sea  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000014</GUID>
      <Text>Arnakuagsak Takirak, Huntress of the sea</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000015</GUID>
      <Text>Just like her brother Nukilik, Arnakuagsak got the way of hunting passed through by her parents. She prefers hunting on the shorelines and the sea.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Arnakuagsak Takirak, Huntress of the sea  -->
  <!-- START Sir Pryce Pryce-Jones, Warm clothing for everyone  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000016</GUID>
      <Text>Sir Pryce Pryce-Jones, Warm clothing for everyone</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000017</GUID>
      <Text>Well known for his entrepreneurship he came up with some good new ideas for insulation in clothing. Perfect to use in sleeping bags, warm parka's and Fur coats.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Sir Pryce Pryce-Jones, Warm clothing for everyone  -->
  <!-- START Jenny Heat, It is not just wood  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000018</GUID>
      <Text>Jenny Heat, It is not just wood</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000019</GUID>
      <Text>Just like her brother Brandon, Jenny found a new home on the Arctic. They both specialized in processing wood. Jenny loves processing basic wood into timber to help build other wooden materials. She learned some special tricks from her brother to create some extra charcoal from the leftover wood.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Jenny Heat, It is not just wood  -->
  <!-- START Aissa Okoro, Smasher of stews  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000020</GUID>
      <Text>Aissa Okoro, Smasher of stews</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000021</GUID>
      <Text>Enbesa was really hot for her, she wanted a colder climate and choose to travel to the Arctic. With her seafood stew cooking knowledge she shows the people in the Arctic that Pemmican can also be made with fish. Sometimes she makes some seafood stew as a memory to her times in Enbesa.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Aissa Okoro, Smasher of stews  -->
  <!-- START Jean-Claude Montagne, The perfect Arctic miner  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000022</GUID>
      <Text>Jean-Claude Montagne, The perfect Arctic miner</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000023</GUID>
      <Text>The oldest of the 3 mining brothers. He perfected mining on the Arctic. Gas mines and deep gold mines do not have any secrets for him anymore. He feels responsible for his two younger brothers after the death of their parents.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Jean-Claude Montagne, The perfect Arctic miner  -->
  <!-- START Jean-François Montagne, The better Arctic miner  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000024</GUID>
      <Text>Jean-François Montagne, The better Arctic miner</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000025</GUID>
      <Text>The middle brother of 3 mining brothers. Mining is what he loves, and mostly in the brute conditions of the Arctic. He looks up to his older brother Jean-Claude, his big example. Together with his two brothers he forms the perfect mining trio for the Arctic. </Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Jean-François Montagne, The better Arctic miner  -->
  <!-- START Jean-Marie Montagne, The sad arctic miner  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000026</GUID>
      <Text>Jean-Marie Montagne, The sad arctic miner</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000027</GUID>
      <Text>The youngest of 3 mining brothers. He actually hates the cold climate of the Arctic but he had no choice and had to follow his 2 older brothers to the Arctic after the death of their parents. </Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Jean-Marie Montagne, The sad arctic miner  -->
  <!-- START Amka Etok, Carve to slide  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000028</GUID>
      <Text>Amka Etok, Carve to slide</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000029</GUID>
      <Text>Amka has a family business together with her brother Toklo. They carve and create husky sleds for all Arctic people. She does not really like the sea and that is why she prefers furs instead of seal skin to create the sleds.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Amka Etok, Carve to slide  -->
  <!-- START Toklo Etok, More then a sled  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000030</GUID>
      <Text>Toklo Etok, More then a sled</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000031</GUID>
      <Text>With his sister Amka, Toklo perfected the creation of husky sleds. But there is more to his knowledge then only sleds. Toklo was once given sketches of Steam Carriages by a traveler. He was so fascinated that he replicates the basic chassis. </Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Toklo Etok, More then a sled  -->
  <!-- START Rolf van der Mark, Breeder of Arctic animals  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000032</GUID>
      <Text>Rolf van der Mark, Breeder of Arctic animals</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000033</GUID>
      <Text>Rolf was always surrounded by animals when he was a child. In contrast with his brother Mark who wanted to produce as much as possible, Rolf wanted to produce as space efficient as possible. They had a business together with their sisters Wendy and Judy but at some point had a huge fight. Rolf could not stand his brother and moved to the Arctic.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Rolf van der Mark, Breeder of Arctic animals  -->
  <!-- START Jumoke Okoro, The Enbesian light  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000034</GUID>
      <Text>Jumoke Okoro, The Enbesian light</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000035</GUID>
      <Text>With his sister Aissa, Jumoke traveled to the Arctic. They fell in love with the beautiful landscapes and snow. In Enbesa Jumoke produced the best lanterns people could wish for. In the Arctic he started working in the Oil lamp factories and used his expertise to improve the process.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Jumoke Okoro, The Enbesian light  -->
  <!-- START Yuka Saunik, Keep warm and light your spirit  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000036</GUID>
      <Text>Yuka Saunik, Keep warm and light your spirit</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000037</GUID>
      <Text>Yuka hates the cold and because of that she wants to keep everyone warm with the perfect clothing and light. Sister of Inuksuk and Umiaktorvik.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Yuka Saunik, Keep warm and light your spirit  -->
  <!-- START Umiaktorvik Saunik, Drinks for everyone  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000038</GUID>
      <Text>Umiaktorvik Saunik, Drinks for everyone</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000039</GUID>
      <Text>Umiaktorvik knows how to please people. If it is alcohol or coffee, he makes sure all people are kept warm with the perfect drink. Brother of Yuka and Inuksuk.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Umiaktorvik Saunik, Drinks for everyone  -->
  <!-- START Inuksuk Saunik, Keep a round belly  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000040</GUID>
      <Text>Inuksuk Saunik, Keep a round belly</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000041</GUID>
      <Text>Inuksuk loves food and shares his love for food with everyone. He wants to keep the bellies of everyone filled en round in those cold times. Brother of Yuka and Umiaktorvik.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Inuksuk Saunik, Keep a round belly  -->
  <!-- START Philipa Sky, Fast, Faster, Fastest  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000042</GUID>
      <Text>Philipa Sky, Fast, Faster, Fastest</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000043</GUID>
      <Text>Her biggest dream as a kid was to fly in the clouds. She pursued her dreams and together with her brother Phillip she helped Old Nate learning to navigate airships.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Philipa Sky, Fast, Faster, Fastest  -->
  <!-- START Phillip Sky, Going with the flow of the wind  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000044</GUID>
      <Text>Phillip Sky, Going with the flow of the wind</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000045</GUID>
      <Text>As the older brother Phillip felt responsible for the dreams of his younger sister Philipa. He actually wanted to become a navy captain but he sacrificied his own dreams for his sister. He met Old Nate and saw an opportunity to help him with his airships and made his sister really happy.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Phillip Sky, Going with the flow of the wind  -->
  <!-- START Colonel Joseph Potts, Expert of foundries  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000046</GUID>
      <Text>Colonel Joseph Potts, Expert of foundries</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000047</GUID>
      <Text>Smelting all types of ores was always a passion in the family. As a good family member Colonel Potts stepped into the family business. He modernized it and made a top priority of safety in the workplace. </Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Colonel Joseph Potts, Expert of foundries  -->
  <!-- START Alessandro Volta, The flow of electricity  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000048</GUID>
      <Text>Alessandro Volta, The flow of electricity</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000049</GUID>
      <Text>Alessandro was groundbraking when it comes to electricity and ways we can transfer electricity. He dedicated his life to share his knowledge to as much people as possible.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Alessandro Volta, The flow of electricity  -->
  <!-- START Thomas Alva Edison, Master of light  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000050</GUID>
      <Text>Thomas Alva Edison, Master of light</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000051</GUID>
      <Text>Thomas Alva Edison perfected and combined different technologies to create the working light bulb that could be mass produced. This opened a lot of possibilities and together with electricity brought safer light to the people.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Thomas Alva Edison, Master of light  -->
  <!-- START Zaire Mto Wa Bluu, Makes the river flow  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000052</GUID>
      <Text>Zaire Mto Wa Bluu, Makes the river flow</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000053</GUID>
      <Text>Water is what he loves. It is the source of all life and really precious in Enbesa. After years of research and new insights, Zaire figured out how to make water pumps more effective and irrigate more land. He is now honored for his contributions.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Zaire Mto Wa Bluu, Makes the river flow  -->
  <!-- START Wendy van der Mark, Breeder of animals  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000054</GUID>
      <Text>Wendy van der Mark, Breeder of animals</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000055</GUID>
      <Text>Together with her 2 brothers Mark and Rolf and sister Judy she started a business. Wendy always looked up to her brother Mark and would never leave his side. When Rolf decided to move to the Arctic and Judy also could no longer stand her brother, Wendy stayed with Mark to keep running the family business.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Wendy van der Mark, Breeder of animals  -->
  <!-- START Judy van der Mark, Sheep and goat lover  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000056</GUID>
      <Text>Judy van der Mark, Sheep and goat lover</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000057</GUID>
      <Text>Judy was always attracted by sheep and goats. Other animals did never really interest her. At some point there were troubles in the familybusiness she started with her 2 brothers and sister. Together with her brother Rolf she left the business. He went to the Arctic but she would not leave her sheep and goats who can not live in that cold climate. She sometimes goes to Enbesa to help the goat farms.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Judy van der Mark, Sheep and goat lover  -->
  <!-- START Zendaya Chedjou, Meat is meat  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000058</GUID>
      <Text>Zendaya Chedjou, Meat is meat</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000059</GUID>
      <Text>From the moment she saw a picture of the Old World, Zendaya had the dream to travel to this unknown country. When she became an adult and had enough money to travel she took the risk and left everything behind to find her happiness in the Old World. She took her expertise with her and now works in the slaughterhouses to process pigs and process the meat to new products unknown for the people of the Old World.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Zendaya Chedjou, Meat is meat  -->
  <!-- START Veronica Castelli, Let it grow with less space  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000060</GUID>
      <Text>Veronica Castelli, Let it grow with less space</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000061</GUID>
      <Text>Veronica has the same love for crops like her brother Cosmo. They both specialise in the crops of the Old world. But Veronica has learned some tricks from the new world and found a solution to harvast corn together with other crops, and that with a smaller amount of fields. She does not like the monoculture and plants trees inside and next to the fields which results in extra fruits.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Veronica Castelli, Let it grow with less space  -->
  <!-- START Alisha Al-Zahir, Less fields more profits  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000062</GUID>
      <Text>Alisha Al-Zahir, Less fields more profits</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000063</GUID>
      <Text>Alisha has her own opinions about the way we grow our crops. She actually thinks we should use less space to give nature something back. She is a big example for het brother Ali and took some research she learned in Enbesa back home to the New World.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Alisha Al-Zahir, Less fields more profits  -->
  <!-- START Abebe Kanumba, Space optimization  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000064</GUID>
      <Text>Abebe Kanumba, Space optimization</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000065</GUID>
      <Text>The dry lands of Enbesa are really hard to grow crops. Abebe made it his goal in life to find better ways to grow crops with less space, which results in less water. He found a way to manipulate seeds to make it possible to grow other crops on the islands of Enbesa.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Abebe Kanumba, Space optimization  -->
  <!-- START Trudy Garnier, Grain is gold  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000066</GUID>
      <Text>Trudy Garnier, Grain is gold</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000067</GUID>
      <Text>Trudy and her brother Marie-Antoine are the perfect baking duo. Trudy takes care of the best grain and her brother then uses that flour to bake some lovely bread. She also likes to make some biscuits in her spare time.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Trudy Garnier, Grain is gold  -->
  <!-- START Dennis Black, Pump it up  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000068</GUID>
      <Text>Dennis Black, Pump it up</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000069</GUID>
      <Text>Dennis could drink oil if it would be possible. He loves the black gold. He has set up some safety procedures to reduce the chance of explosions drasticly.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Dennis Black, Pump it up  -->
  <!-- START Lucy Roberts, Power to the people  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000070</GUID>
      <Text>Lucy Roberts, Power to the people</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000071</GUID>
      <Text>Lucy is the expert if it comes to power plants. If it is an oil based or gas based power plant, she has it covered. Safety first is her motto.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Lucy Roberts, Power to the people  -->
  <!-- START Macy Parker, No rendering no glory  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000072</GUID>
      <Text>Macy Parker, No rendering no glory</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000073</GUID>
      <Text>Macy specialises in processing pigs and tallow. Tallow has no secrets anymore for her. She researched other processes with pigs and tallow and found out she could extract other goods from them.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Macy Parker, No rendering no glory  -->
  <!-- START Maurice Dupont, Give the tractors some juice  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000074</GUID>
      <Text>Maurice Dupont, Give the tractors some juice</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000075</GUID>
      <Text>As a kid Maurice saw the technological advancements go by and tractors fascinated him from the start. When he grew up his goal was to ride one of those fantastic machines. When he finaly was able to fulfil his dream he focused on maximising the output of oil needed by the tractors.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Maurice Dupont, Give the tractors some juice  -->
  <!-- START Polly Davies, Is it running?  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000076</GUID>
      <Text>Polly Davies, Is it running</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000077</GUID>
      <Text>Polly loves machines. As one of the best engineers she knows almost every motor inside out. Almost ever machine that uses a motor has been dismantled and put back together by her.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Polly Davies, Is it running?  -->
  <!-- START Curtis Blink, Make it shiny  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000078</GUID>
      <Text>Curtis Blink, Make it shiny</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000079</GUID>
      <Text>Curtis does not like to work with coal. He uses wood instead of coal to melt the gold ore. He experiments to get other types of materials.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Curtis Blink, Make it shiny  -->
  <!-- START Hendrick Harrison, Up and down  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000080</GUID>
      <Text>Hendrick Harrison, Up and down</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000081</GUID>
      <Text>Elevators make the life of many people so much easier. Hendrick was one of the first people using an elevator and was really impressed. But from his perspective an elevator should be with a view to the outside. That is why he prefers to use glass and not wood veneers.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Hendrick Harrison, Up and down  -->
  <!-- START Jacques Brun, Baking chocolat biscuits  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000082</GUID>
      <Text>Jacques Brun, Baking chocolat biscuits</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000083</GUID>
      <Text>Jacques is the big rival of Marie-Antoine. They both love to bake and challenge eachother in baking contests. Last time they were at a contest they had a huge fight and almost destroyed eachothers creations. The jury had to come inbetween them. And they both were disqualified.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Jacques Brun, Baking chocolat biscuits  -->
  <!-- START Henry Mill, Typing 24/7  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000084</GUID>
      <Text>Henry Mill, Typing 24/7</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000085</GUID>
      <Text>Henry was one of the first persons who thought about putting letters in a sequence on paper that would result in a new machine, a typewriter.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Henry Mill, Typing 24/7  -->
  <!-- START Zola Kanumba, Mixing the forest seeds  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000086</GUID>
      <Text>Zola Kanumba, Mixing the forest seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000087</GUID>
      <Text>Zola does not like the monoculture of the orchyards. She mixes things up to make sure all those beautiful, colorful blossoms are mixed together to create amazing views in the Old World and the New World.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Zola Kanumba, Mixing the forest seeds  -->
  <!-- START Kofi Adomako, Cigars & Pipes  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000088</GUID>
      <Text>Kofi Adomako, Cigars and Pipes</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000089</GUID>
      <Text>In Enbesa he was known for his quality clay pipes. He traveled to the New World to learn more about cigars. He was so inspired that he left his brother Adamo in Enbesa and stayed in the New World.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Kofi Adomako, Cigars & Pipes  -->
  <!-- START Mildred Mitchell, Tailormade  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000090</GUID>
      <Text>Mildred Mitchell, Tailormade</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000091</GUID>
      <Text>Mildred is one of the finest knitters of the Old World. At a certain point he was tired of those boring Old World clothing designs that he went to Enbesa to learn more about the colorful clothing from this fantastic world. He came back to the Old World with so many new ideas.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Mildred Mitchell, Tailormade  -->
  <!-- START Alexander Graham Bell, Calling home  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000092</GUID>
      <Text>Alexander Graham Bell, Calling home</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000093</GUID>
      <Text>Alexander Graham Bell was one of the founders of the first telephone and made his mark in history. </Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Alexander Graham Bell, Calling home  -->
  <!-- START Mariana Soto, Weaving till you drop  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000094</GUID>
      <Text>Mariana Soto, Weaving till you drop</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000095</GUID>
      <Text>Mariana knows every textile and fibre inside out. Weaving has no secrets for her. She discovered ways to make paper from textiles.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Mariana Soto, Weaving till you drop  -->
  <!-- START Gertrude von Malching, Digging for gold  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000096</GUID>
      <Text>Gertrude von Malching, Digging for gold</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000097</GUID>
      <Text>Mining is a family tradition. Like her brothers Jörg and Fritz, Gertrude is always looking for ways to improve the mining business. She decided to focus on the gold mining business in the New World because the time it takes to extract gold there is not good enough. She developed amazing new ways to boost the production to a amazing level. Number 6 is her lucky number.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Gertrude von Malching, Digging for gold  -->
  <!-- START Ana Paula Vargas, I like sugar and cannot lie  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000098</GUID>
      <Text>Ana Paula Vargas, I like sugar and cannot lie</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000099</GUID>
      <Text>Sugar is the white gold for Ana Paula. She loves to make so many things with it. In the future she will make sure there will be more goods that use her sugar. She loves beer with a sweet touch.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Ana Paula Vargas, I like sugar and cannot lie  -->
  <!-- START Juliana Perez, Wool is the answer  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000100</GUID>
      <Text>Juliana Perez, Wool is the answer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000101</GUID>
      <Text>Juliana has lost her heart in Enbesa. She traveled there from the New World and not only fell in love with the beautiful continent but also with a woman, Hibo Ameziane. Together they started a clothing business. Juliana takes care of the raw materials and her partner Hibo Ameziane processes those to beautiful clothing that keep the Enbesan people warm and stylish. She has some nice tricks on her sleeve to process the raw materials to new goods.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Juliana Perez, Wool is the answer  -->
  <!-- START Hibo Ameziane, Stylish clothing  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000102</GUID>
      <Text>Hibo Ameziane, Stylish clothing</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000103</GUID>
      <Text>Hibo is one of the best clothing makers from Enbesa. Together with her partner Juliana Perez who fell in love with Enbesa and Hibo, she started a clothing business. Hibo makes the most amazing clothing to keep the people of Enbesa warm and stylish at the same time.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Hibo Ameziane, Stylish clothing  -->
  <!-- START Ghudan Keita, The finest looms  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000104</GUID>
      <Text>Ghudan Keita, The finest looms</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000105</GUID>
      <Text>The finest tapestries of Enbesa are made by Ghudan. Some people say she has golden fingers, but she actually uses the newest looms to be more precise and efficient. With the leftovers she weaves finery.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Ghudan Keita, The finest looms  -->
  <!-- START Rua Okoro, With the tides of the sea  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000106</GUID>
      <Text>Rua Okoro, With the tides of the sea</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000107</GUID>
      <Text>Sister of Aissa and Jumoke who both went to the Arctic. She was left behind in Enbesa but did not want to go to the Arctic. She focuses on the Saltworks and optimizing the process and extracting more goods from the sea with the tides.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Rua Okoro, With the tides of the sea  -->
  <!-- START Danen Bamidele, These boots are made for walking  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000108</GUID>
      <Text>Danen Bamidele, These boots are made for walking</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000109</GUID>
      <Text>Danen was always intriged by what he could do with animal materials. When he was working in the Dry-houses he saw a lot of the materials go to waste. He encourages to use everything and makes leather boots on the side.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Danen Bamidele, These boots are made for walking  -->
  <!-- START Frank Keinehen, He loves beer  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000110</GUID>
      <Text>Frank Keinehen, He loves beer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000111</GUID>
      <Text>Frank is known for his unusual use of ingredients for beer. He has made a wide variety of sorts of beer. His latest creation is beer from Hibiscus petals.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Frank Keinehen, He loves beer  -->
  <!-- START Fritz von Malching, Mining on the surface  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000112</GUID>
      <Text>Fritz von Malching, Mining on the surface</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000113</GUID>
      <Text>As the youngest of the von Malching mining family, Fritz is a bit claustrofobic and does not like to go in small tunnels inside the mountains to mine the precious ores. When he heard that in Enbesa they mine on the surface in rivers he decided to go to Enbesa and see how he could improve this type of mining with his family expertise. </Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Fritz von Malching, Mining on the surface  -->
  <!-- START Margaret Lee, Clay and sand  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000114</GUID>
      <Text>Margaret Lee, Clay and sand</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000115</GUID>
      <Text>Margaret was always playing in the clay pits when she was a child. Her parents were really poor and working hard to make a living and giving Margaret a better future. When Margaret grew older she could not get the best work experience even though she has so many good skills with clay. The only job she could find was in the Brick Dry-House. She makes the best out of it and sometimes creates ceramics in her spare time to show her love for clay.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Margaret Lee, Clay and sand -->
  <!-- START Mariette Brun, No pain no grain -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000116</GUID>
      <Text>Mariette Brun, No pain no grain</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000117</GUID>
      <Text>Mariette is the sister of Jacques who is also in the baking business. Mariette left the Old World for the exotic Enbesa to explore new lands. There she realised grain was something she could actually also use as a replacement for teff.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Mariette Brun, No pain no grain -->
  <!-- START Ayaan Chedjou, Canned food is better food -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000118</GUID>
      <Text>Ayaan Chedjou, Canned meat is better meat</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000119</GUID>
      <Text>When she visited her sister Zendaya in the Old World she discovered the beauty of canned food. When she came back to Enbesa she decided to use this technique to conserve food longer and make sure no food was spilled when making stew.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Ayaan Chedjou, Canned food is better food -->
  <!-- START Adamo Adomako, Pipes & Cigars -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000120</GUID>
      <Text>Adamo Adomako, Pipes and Cigars</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000121</GUID>
      <Text>Together with his brother Kofi, Adamo was always to be found on the tabaco fields to find the best quality for their clay pipes. On their travels to the New World they learned about the cigars they make in the New World. When his brother decided to stay in the New World Adamo still wanted to go back home to Enbesa, but he took the knowledge of the cigars with him.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Adamo Adomako, Pipes & Cigars -->
  <!-- START Elgizouli Nnamani, The keeper of the golden bees -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000122</GUID>
      <Text>Elgizouli Nnamani, The keeper of the golden bees</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000123</GUID>
      <Text>People are not the best friends of Elgizouli, he prefers his bees. He is also a big lover of flowers which is the perfect combination together with his bees.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Elgizouli Nnamani, The keeper of the golden bees -->
  <!-- START Kwame Aku, The perfect candles -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000124</GUID>
      <Text>Kwame Aku, The perfect candles</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000125</GUID>
      <Text>Kwame has golden hands which he uses to make the perfect candles. He changed some basic principles in the process which results in extracting ethanol even he uses the same base products. The perfect candles he makes are then processed by his sister Makena to beautiful lanterns.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Kwame Aku, The perfect candles -->
  <!-- START Makena Aku, Bringer of light -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000126</GUID>
      <Text>Makena Aku, Bringer of light</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000127</GUID>
      <Text>Makena always loved to carve objects out of the strong wanza timber. She perfected to art of carving lanterns out of wanza wood. This wood is so strong it can stand the heat of the candles inside. The perfect candles she gets from her brother Kwame.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Makena Aku, Bringer of light -->
  <!-- START Catherina Hendrika, The first journalist -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000128</GUID>
      <Text>Catherina Hendrika, The first journalist</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000129</GUID>
      <Text>When typewriters became a thing Catherina saw the opportunity to start writing for the University newspaper faster than before. She provides the Scholars with the perfect news to make them happy. On her free time she likes to cuddle her cat and work in the garden to see her flowers bloom.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Catherina Hendrika, The first journalist -->
  <!-- START Maya The Cat, Purring to happiness -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000130</GUID>
      <Text>Maya The Cat, Purring to happiness</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000131</GUID>
      <Text>Nobody has ever seen a more joyful and lovely cat than Maya. She provides the hotel guests with her warm presence and welcomes every new and returning guest with a nice purr. </Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Maya The Cat, Purring to happiness -->
  <!-- START Yared Aguta, Shiny no color -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000132</GUID>
      <Text>Yared Aguta, Shiny no color</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000133</GUID>
      <Text>Yared wanted ceramics to have more value. With adding pearls instead of coloring them he created a new type of ceramics that were popular with a wide variety of people. He also makes ceramics jewellery the same time.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Yared Aguta, Shiny no color -->
  <!-- START Rupert Flanders, Homeschooling -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000134</GUID>
      <Text>Rupert Flanders, Homeschooling</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000135</GUID>
      <Text>Rupert is a believer of homeschooling. We do not have to go to public schools or universities to learn new things. We can do this at home with the right guidance.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Rupert Flanders, Homeschooling -->
  <!-- START Jacky Daniels, Drinks for the rich -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000136</GUID>
      <Text>Jacky Daniels, Boissons pour les riches</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000137</GUID>
      <Text>Jacky buvait du whisky depuis son plus jeune âge. Mais une fois qu'elle a goûté au cognac, elle ne voulait plus rien boire d'autre. Cela n'amusait pas sa famille, mais elle s'en fichait. Outre le cognac, elle a également découvert le rhum et le champagne.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Jacky Daniels, Drinks for the rich -->
  <!-- START Brian Branch, Basic wooden tables -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000138</GUID>
      <Text>Brian Branch, Tables de base en bois</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000139</GUID>
      <Text>Brian et sa famille travaillent dans le domaine du bois et mettent au point un grand nombre de produits en bois différents pour le Vieux Monde. Il se concentre sur la simplification des tables de billard. Elles sont désormais fabriquées avec du bois normal et non plus avec du cerisier de luxe.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Brian Branch, Basic wooden tables -->
  <!-- START Brook Branch, Pure wood no shiny lacquer -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000140</GUID>
      <Text>Brook Branch, Du bois pur, pas de laque brillante.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000141</GUID>
      <Text>Brook et sa famille travaillent dans le domaine du bois et perfectionnent de nombreux produits en bois pour l'Ancien Monde. Son objectif est de fabriquer des violons sans laque toxique et avec une finition en bois magnifique. Pour cette finition, elle utilise des placages en bois et non de la laque. Elle joue elle-même du violon et est un musicien bien connu dans l'Ancien Monde. Elle crée également des gramophones pour diffuser sa musique aux gens.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Brook Branch, Pure wood no shiny lacquer -->
  <!-- START Brandon Branch, Wooden toys -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000142</GUID>
      <Text>Brandon Branch, Brandon Branch, Jouets en bois</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000143</GUID>
      <Text>Brian et sa famille travaillent dans le domaine du bois et perfectionnent de nombreux produits en bois pour le Vieux Monde. Il se concentre sur les jouets en bois pour enfants. Il n'a jamais aimé le fait que les jouets soient aujourd'hui fabriqués en celluloïd et finis avec une laque toxique. Il les remplace par des alternatives en bois pur pour obtenir de beaux jouets en bois avec lesquels les enfants peuvent jouer. En outre, certains de ces jouets peuvent également être utilisés comme souvenirs pour les touristes.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Brandon Branch, Wooden toys -->
  <!-- START Irene Braunkopf, Curly fresh hair -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000144</GUID>
      <Text>Irene Braunkopf, Des cheveux frais et bouclés</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000145</GUID>
      <Text>Irène travaillait comme coiffeuse lorsqu'elle a découvert que les shampooings avaient un potentiel beaucoup plus important. Elle a commencé à tester de nouvelles formules chez elle et a découvert de nouveaux parfums frais. Avec ces nouvelles formules, elle a simplifié une grande partie des processus.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Irene Braunkopf, Curly fresh hair -->
  <!-- START John Lemon, Sugarfree lemonade -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000146</GUID>
      <Text>John Lemon, Limonade sans sucre</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000147</GUID>
      <Text>John n'aime pas le sucre, c'est un mal pour notre santé. Il met en bouteille de la limonade sans aucun additif sucre et le remplace par des pétales d'hibiscus comme goût supplémentaire.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END John Lemon, Sugarfree lemonade -->
  <!-- START Britt Branch, Wooden souvenirs -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000148</GUID>
      <Text>Britt Branch, Souvenirs en bois</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000149</GUID>
      <Text>Britt et sa famille travaillent dans le domaine du bois et perfectionnent un grand nombre de produits en bois différents pour le Vieux Monde. Elle se concentre sur la fabrication de souvenirs en bois. Cela donne lieu à de nouveaux types de souvenirs magnifiques, fabriqués à partir des meilleurs bois. Certains de ces souvenirs peuvent également être utilisés comme jouets.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Britt Branch, Wooden souvenirs -->
  <!-- START Denise Blink, Lacquer efficiency -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000150</GUID>
      <Text>Denise Blink, Efficacité de la laque</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000151</GUID>
      <Text>Comme son frère Curtis, Denise aime les objets brillants. La façon dont la laque rend les surfaces plus brillantes lui donne des frissons. Elle a perfectionné le processus de laquage pour utiliser moins de matériaux.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Denise Blink, Lacquer efficiency -->
  <!-- START Ernesto Vargas, No sugar, pure banana -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000152</GUID>
      <Text>Ernesto Vargas, Pas de sucre, de la banane pure</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000153</GUID>
      <Text>Ernesto est tout le contraire de sa sœur Ana Paula. Il n'aime pas le sucre et veut en utiliser le moins possible. Il se concentre sur le chewing-gum et a décidé de supprimer les sucres additifs et de les remplacer par des bananes plantains.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Ernesto Vargas, No sugar, pure banana -->
  <!-- START Francesco Plastmasa, Celluloid efficiency -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000154</GUID>
      <Text>Francesco Plastmasa, L'efficacité du celluloïd</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000155</GUID>
      <Text>Avec sa sœur Francesca, Francesco était toujours à la recherche de nouveaux matériaux et de moyens d'améliorer les produits. Lorsqu'ils ont découvert ce qu'ils pouvaient faire avec la cire de camphre et l'éthanol, il a cherché des moyens plus efficaces d'utiliser ces matériaux dans le processus de fabrication du celluloïd.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Francesco Plastmasa, Celluloid efficiency -->
  <!-- START Francesca Plastmasa, Ethanol overdrive -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000156</GUID>
      <Text>Francesca Plastmasa, Ethanol overdrive</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000157</GUID>
      <Text>Avec son frère Francesco, Francesca était toujours à la recherche de nouveaux matériaux et de moyens d'améliorer les produits. Elle a vu de nouvelles opportunités dans le processus de fabrication de l'éthanol et a amélioré ce processus encore plus.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Francesca Plastmasa, Ethanol overdrive -->
  <!-- START Marco Paulo, Spicing things up -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000158</GUID>
      <Text>Marco Paulo, Spicing things up</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000159</GUID>
      <Text>Marco likes the taste of spicy food. He always makes food with that extra spicy taste. A good meal need to have a good spicy sauce to be perfect.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Marco Paulo, Spicing things up -->
  <!-- START Sister Moppertus, Drinks from the hacienda -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000160</GUID>
      <Text>Sister Moppertus, Drinks from the hacienda</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000161</GUID>
      <Text>Sister Moppertus first devoted her life to god, but saw Brother Hilarius doing amazing work with making interesting drinks. She decided to devote her life more to the hacienda optimazation and the different drinks that are made there. She did not carer if this is with gods consent or not. She loves alcohol.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Sister Moppertus, Drinks from the hacienda -->
  <!-- START Lena Brown, Fertiliser from the woods -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000162</GUID>
      <Text>Lena Brown, Fertiliser from the woods</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000163</GUID>
      <Text>Lena is the sister of Gretl Brown and the daughter of Lukas Brown. Like her father she was interested in how we can improve our farmlands with fertiliser. But in contrast with her father she wanted more existing natural resources to be used for fertiliser and focuses on the wonders of the woods to produce fertiliser.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Lena Brown, Fertiliser from the woods -->
  <!-- START Lukas Brown, Collector of dung -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000164</GUID>
      <Text>Lukas Brown, Collector of dung</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000165</GUID>
      <Text>Lukas is the father of Gretl and Lena Brown. Lukas can always be found near animal farms. He discovered the potential of dung from visiting the New World. With some brown magic he processes the dung immediatly to fertiliser, ready to use on the farmlands.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Lukas Brown, Collector of dung -->
  <!-- START Valentina de Faro, Chocolat, Coffee and biscuits -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000166</GUID>
      <Text>Valentina de Faro, Chocolat, café et biscuits</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000167</GUID>
      <Text>Valentina est la grande sœur de Fernando de Faro. Fernando a appris à faire le meilleur café de Valentina qui a appris de leur père qui est décédé il y a de nombreuses années. Ils sont tous deux passés par la voie du café, mais Valentina connaît plus que le café, elle aime le goût sucré du chocolat et des biscuits.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Valentina de Faro, Chocolat, Coffee and biscuits -->
  <!-- START Mrs Garrick, Money and Shiny things are not the answer -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000168</GUID>
      <Text>Mme Garrick, L'argent et les objets brillants ne sont pas la solution</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000169</GUID>
      <Text>Mme Garrick est la sœur de M. Garrick. Elle n'aime pas les produits chers et la banque.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Mrs Garrick, Money and Shiny things are not the answer -->
  <!-- START Georgina Ravenscroft, Inventor of modern sand collecting -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000170</GUID>
      <Text>Georgina Ravenscroft, inventeur du ramassage moderne du sable</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000171</GUID>
      <Text>La verrerie a toujours fait partie de l'empire Ravenscroft, mais c'est Georgina qui a considérablement automatisé et raccourci le processus de collecte et d'extraction du sable.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Georgina Ravenscroft, Inventor of modern sand collecting -->
  <!-- START Lola Mazigh, Persuader of the sea -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000172</GUID>
      <Text>Lola Mazigh, Persuadée de la mer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000173</GUID>
      <Text>Lola est la sœur de Lalla Mazigh et donc aussi une parente de Mme Kahina. Si Lola fait partie de l'équipage d'un navire, aucun navire n'ose l'attaquer. Elle a la voix la plus douce qui puisse faire du plus grand ennemi un ami.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Lola Mazigh, Persuader of the sea -->
  <!-- START Lou Mazigh, Perfect trading routes -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000174</GUID>
      <Text>Lou Mazigh, Des routes commerciales parfaites</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000175</GUID>
      <Text>Lou est le père de Lola et Lalla. Comme sa fille Lola, il aime naviguer en mer et sentir le vent. Il s'est concentré sur l'optimisation des navires afin d'obtenir un meilleur niveau d'efficacité pour son activité commerciale.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- START Flappy, The best Arctic friend -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000176</GUID>
      <Text>Flappy, le meilleur ami arctique</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000177</GUID>
      <Text>Flappy est le meilleur ami de Carsten Green, qui a domestiqué Flappy depuis qu'il était un chiot. Flappy a été laissé seul par ses parents dans les bois où Carsten l'a trouvé. Flappy est maintenant toujours aux côtés de Carsten lorsqu'ils se promènent dans les bois. Flappy illumine l'esprit des habitants de l'Arctique.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Flappy, The best Arctic friend -->
  <!-- START Flippy, Flippin awesome -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000178</GUID>
      <Text>Flippy, Flippin génial</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000179</GUID>
      <Text>Nous connaissons tous des chiens qui sont tout simplement géniaux. Flippy est l'un de ces chiens. Il aime jouer avec des jouets qui couinent, mais, aussi génial qu'il soit, lorsqu'il entend un couinement, il est tellement choqué qu'il saute d'un mètre dans les airs.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Flippy, Flippin awesome -->
  <!-- START Floppy, Herder of animals -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000180</GUID>
      <Text>Floppy, éleveur d'animaux</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000181</GUID>
      <Text>Floppy est un chien de troupeau de 4ème génération. La famille de Floppy a toujours fait partie de la famille Van der Mark et a aidé la famille Van der Mark à développer son empire d'élevage d'animaux. Sans Floppy et sa famille, l'entreprise ne serait pas aussi prospère.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Floppy, Herder of animals -->
  <!-- START Kulwa Mto Wa Bluu, Less damage more speed & cargo -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000182</GUID>
      <Text>Kulwa Mto Wa Bluu, moins de dégâts, plus de vitesse et de cargaison.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000183</GUID>
      <Text>Kulwa est la sœur jumelle de Zaire. Tous deux aimant l'eau, Kulwa a décidé de quitter la terre et son frère pour aller sur la mer et explorer de nouvelles terres. Elle a consacré son service aux navires militaires pour s'assurer que les cargaisons qu'ils contiennent ne les retiennent pas.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Kulwa Mto Wa Bluu, Less damage more speed & cargo -->
  <!-- START Torpedo Of Doom -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000184</GUID>
      <Text>Torpille du destin</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000185</GUID>
      <Text>La torpille ultime, aucun navire ne survivra à cet impact.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Torpedo Of Doom -->
  <!-- START Ultra Rapid Canister shot -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000186</GUID>
      <Text>Ultra Rapid Canister shot</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000187</GUID>
      <Text>La guerre granulaire ultime. Les bombes volent plus vite que jamais.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Ultra Rapid Canister shot -->
  <!-- START Sea Mine Of Death -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000188</GUID>
      <Text>Mine marine de la mort</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000189</GUID>
      <Text>Mettez ces mines légendaires sous la surface et personne ne passera.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Sea Mine Of Death -->
  <!-- START Auto-Controllable-Pitch Propeller -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000190</GUID>
      <Text>Hélice à pas variable</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000191</GUID>
      <Text>L'ultime hélice légendaire pour tous les bateaux à vapeur.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Auto-Controllable-Pitch Propeller -->
  <!-- START Doctor Edward Davy, A Healthy Lifestyle -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000195</GUID>
      <Text>Docteur Edward Davy, un mode de vie sain</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000196</GUID>
      <Text>Le docteur Edward Davy est un fervent partisan d'un mode de vie sain. Il convainc ses patients de continuer à faire du vélo au lieu d'utiliser ces sales et malsaines voitures à vapeur. Il montre l'exemple et partout où il va, il prend son vélo. Il est également contre le fait de fumer des cigares et vous fera un sermon sur le caractère malsain de la cigarette.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Doctor Edward Davy, A Healthy Lifestyle -->
  <!-- START Helga Hogarth, Airship Platform Master Of Arms -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000197</GUID>
      <Text>Helga Hogarth, maître d'armes de la plate-forme des dirigeables.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000198</GUID>
      <Text>Sœur du célèbre Hogarth The Harbourmaster, vétéran de Trelawney. Comme son frère, elle s'intéresse au chargement et au déchargement des navires. Elle met au point une méthode efficace pour charger et décharger les navires plus rapidement.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END  Helga Hogarth, Airship Platform Master Of Arms -->
  <!-- START  Captain Pirtylo, Scouting From The Sky -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000200</GUID>
      <Text>Capitaine Pirtylo, éclaireur du ciel</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000201</GUID>
      <Text>Le capitaine Pirtylo s'élance vers le ciel à bord d'énormes dirigeables. Lorsqu'il était enfant, il a perdu l'un de ses meilleurs amis qui a été enlevé par des pirates. Il a juré qu'il retrouverait son ami quand il serait grand. Jusqu'à ce jour, il vole à travers le monde à la recherche de son ami perdu, en espérant qu'un jour il le retrouvera.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Captain Pirtylo, Scouting From The Sky -->
  <!-- START Joseph Christians, Talking Sense Into People -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000202</GUID>
      <Text>Joseph Christians, pour faire entendre raison aux gens</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000203</GUID>
      <Text>Joseph est le mari de Marie la folle. Il voit sa femme faire des choses folles dans les mines sans penser à ce qui pourrait arriver. Il contrebalance ces idées folles et s'assure que tout se déroule selon (son) plan.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Joseph Christians, Talking Sense Into People -->
  <!-- START Pirate Captain's Black Sail -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000204</GUID>
      <Text>La voile noire du capitaine pirate</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000205</GUID>
      <Text>Avec cette voile noire légendaire, chaque navire peut distancer un adversaire à voile.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Pirate Captain's Black Sail -->
  <!-- START Oliver Thorlof, The Happiest Cool Postman -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000206</GUID>
      <Text>Oliver Thorlof, le facteur le plus cool du monde</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000207</GUID>
      <Text>Oliver a la communication dans le sang. Il suit cette passion en étant un facteur heureux pour tout le monde dans l'Arctique. Il distribue chaque lettre à chacun personnellement à travers le froid de l'Arctique, rendant tous les destinataires heureux.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Oliver Thorlof, The Happiest Cool Postman -->
  <!-- START Cecce Celeste, Postman Manager -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000208</GUID>
      <Text>Cecce Celeste, facteur manager</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000209</GUID>
      <Text>Céleste n'est pas une postière normale. Elle gère tous les bureaux de poste de l'Ancien et du Nouveau Monde. Elle attend le meilleur de tous les facteurs, qu'ils remettent chaque lettre avec un grand sourire aux destinataires.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Cecce Celeste, Postman Manager -->
  <!-- START ALL OW AND NW POST OFFICES AND POST BOXES -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000199</GUID>
      <Text>Tous les bureaux de poste et boîtes aux lettres de l'Ancien et du Nouveau Monde</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL OW AND NW POST OFFICES AND POST BOXES -->
  <!-- START Birdy Bird, Fastest Air Messages -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000210</GUID>
      <Text>Birdy Bird, le plus rapide des messages aériens</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000211</GUID>
      <Text>Le pigeon du facteur Oliver. Il distribue chaque lettre de fenêtre en fenêtre sans hésiter. C'est le facteur Oliver qui a formé ce pigeon pour qu'il devienne le parfait pigeon de la poste. Lorsque les gens voient Birdy passer, ils lui font signe et jettent des grains sur le sol pour qu'il les mange.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Birdy Bird, Fastest Air Messages -->
  <!-- START Raveena Bhargava, The Airship Architect -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000212</GUID>
      <Text>Raveena Bhargava, l'architecte du dirigeable</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000213</GUID>
      <Text>Raveena est la sœur de Rohit. Comme son frère, elle a consacré sa vie à la construction de vaisseaux. Elle a toujours voulu être une inventrice et poursuit toujours ce rêve à la recherche de nouvelles technologies.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Raveena Bhargava, The Airship Architect -->
  <!-- START Ron Rogers, Forger Of Fake Mail -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000214</GUID>
      <Text>Ron Rogers, falsificateur de faux courrier</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000215</GUID>
      <Text>Ron a déjà été plusieurs fois en prison pour avoir falsifié des documents. Chaque fois qu'il sort de prison, il recommence. Cette fois, il a trouvé un business dans la fabrication de faux courriers et la vente de fausses histoires.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Ron Rogers, Forger Of Fake Mail -->
  <!-- START Brenda Ironbright, The War Must Go On -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000216</GUID>
      <Text>Brenda Ironbright, la guerre doit continuer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000217</GUID>
      <Text>Brenda est la petite sœur de Bruno Ironbright. Tous deux ont trouvé sans honte le moyen de produire des armes à grande échelle. Les armes ne sont pas toujours la solution, mais ce n'est pas ainsi que Brenda voit les choses. Tirer d'abord, poser des questions ensuite, telle est sa devise.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Brenda Ironbright, The War Must Go On -->
  <!-- START ALL OW AND NW BOMB FACTORIES AND SEA MINE FACTORIES -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000218</GUID>
      <Text>Toutes les usines de bombes et de mines marines de l'Ancien et du Nouveau Monde.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL OW AND NW BOMB FACTORIES AND SEA MINE FACTORIES -->
  <!-- START Edsan Orantes, Play With The Ball -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000219</GUID>
      <Text>Edsan Orantes, Jouer avec le ballon</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000220</GUID>
      <Text>Edsan a toujours été un fan de football ou de soccer, quel que soit le nom qu'on lui donne. Enfant, il jouait toujours avec ses amis et plus tard, il en a fait sa carrière. Maintenant qu'il est à la retraite, il consacre sa vie à produire des ballons et à rendre les enfants heureux avec des versions adaptées à leurs besoins.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Edsan Orantes, Play With The Ball -->
  <!-- START Jacobus Fussall, Ice Cream For Everyone -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000221</GUID>
      <Text>Jacobus Fussall, la crème glacée pour tous</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000222</GUID>
      <Text>Jacobus a trouvé des moyens parfaits de fabriquer des crèmes glacées en masse et a perfectionné le processus en choisissant les bons ingrédients. Il privilégie la saveur de la crème glacée à la noix de coco et essaie d'équilibrer la quantité de sucre. Il combine la crème glacée avec un biscuit.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Jacobus Fussall, Ice Cream For Everyone -->
  <!-- START Koko Flanel, Healthy Perfumes -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000223</GUID>
      <Text>Koko Flanel, Parfums sains</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000224</GUID>
      <Text>Koko détestait l'état actuel de l'industrie de la beauté et l'utilisation de produits chimiques et d'alcool dans tant de produits. Elle a décidé de créer sa propre formule sans tous ces additifs et utilise des produits plus respectueux de la peau. Son parfum n'est pas à vaporiser mais à étaler sur la peau. </Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Koko Flanel, Healthy Perfumes -->
  <!-- START Alfred Lowman, Natural Herbs Cure Everything -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000225</GUID>
      <Text>Alfred Lowman, les herbes naturelles guérissent tout</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000226</GUID>
      <Text>Alfred Lowman est convaincu que nous pouvons tout soigner avec les bonnes herbes et les plantes que nous trouvons dans la nature. En regardant autour de nous, nous pouvons créer les meilleurs médicaments et guérir toutes les maladies. En cas de doute, prenez une tisane !</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Alfred Lowman, Natural Herbs Cure Everything -->
  <!-- START Holario Javino, Dance Dance Baby -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000227</GUID>
      <Text>Holario Javino, Danse Danse Baby</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000228</GUID>
      <Text>Holario a consacré sa vie à la musique Samba et à rendre les gens heureux. Pour lui, c'est un mode de vie et il danse toujours dans les lieux publics et encourage les gens à faire de même. Il rend les gens heureux en dansant. Nous devrions danser, chanter et être heureux ! Pas aller à la guerre, à l'église ou dans une arène de boxe.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Holario Javino, Dance Dance Baby -->
  <!-- START General Agnes Mercier, Anarchist Propaganda -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000229</GUID>
      <Text>Général Agnès Mercier, Propagande anarchiste</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000230</GUID>
      <Text>Le général Agnès est la sœur d'Hugo Mercier. Comme son frère, elle a été élevée à la manière anarchiste. Le cinéma et les films sont le moyen idéal pour montrer aux gens comment ils doivent vivre leur vie et rester sur le "bon" chemin. Ce n'est pas de la propagande si c'est vrai, n'est-ce pas ?</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END General Agnes Mercier, Anarchist Propaganda -->
  <!-- START Josephine Grey, Fertiliser Everywhere -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000231</GUID>
      <Text>Joséphine Grey, Fertiliser partout</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000232</GUID>
      <Text>Joséphine est l'épouse de Lucas Brown. Comme son mari, elle entretient une relation étrange avec le fumier et son utilisation comme engrais. En utilisant certains procédés spécifiques, elle extrait de l'éthanol pendant le processus de fertilisation. </Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Josephine Grey, Fertiliser Everywhere -->
  <!-- START Bio Dung Fertiliser -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000233</GUID>
      <Text>Engrais à base de fumier biologique</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000234</GUID>
      <Text>Un engrais à base de fumier avec quelques additifs bio pour une optimisation supplémentaire. Il sent un peu mauvais, mais qui s'en soucie ?</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Bio Dung Fertiliser -->
  <!-- START Henrich Morris, Space Efficient Storage -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000408</GUID>
      <Text>Henrich Morris, Space Efficient Storage</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000409</GUID>
      <Text>Henrich a créé une entreprise de stockage avec sa femme Roberta. Ils formaient un duo fantastique et n'ont pas tardé à trouver des moyens plus efficaces de stocker des marchandises dans le même espace. Un meilleur inventaire, un meilleur rangement, et quand ils mettent quelque chose dans un entrepôt, il ne se perd jamais. Mais bien sûr, cela a un prix.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Henrich Morris, Space Efficient Storage -->
  <!-- START Roberta Dompson, Layered Storage Solutions -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000410</GUID>
      <Text>Roberta Dompson, Layered Storage Solutions</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000411</GUID>
      <Text>Roberta a créé une entreprise de stockage avec son mari Henrich. Lors de leur voyage de noces en Arctique, Roberta est également tombée amoureuse de la beauté de la neige et des paysages de l'Arctique. D'un point de vue professionnel, elle a vu de nombreuses opportunités d'améliorer les possibilités de stockage dans les conditions arctiques. Mais pas sans les investissements nécessaires.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Roberta Dompson, Layered Storage Solutions -->
  <!-- START Ferdinand Da Edificio, Monuments Will Rise Everywhere -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000412</GUID>
      <Text>Ferdinand Da Edificio, les monuments s'élèveront partout</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000413</GUID>
      <Text>Ferdinand est un ingénieur en bâtiment spécialisé dans les grands bâtiments, les monuments. Comparé à ses collègues du bâtiment, il connaît des astuces pour rendre la construction de monuments plus efficace et plus sûre. Le ciel est la limite, plus le bâtiment est grand, plus il aime ça.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Ferdinand Da Edificio, Monuments Will Rise Everywhere -->
  <!-- START ALL MONUMENTS  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000414</GUID>
      <Text>Toutes les phases de la construction de monuments</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL MONUMENTS  -->
  <!-- START Frotz Wogmann, Inventor Of Synthetic Rubber -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000415</GUID>
      <Text>Frotz Wogmann, inventeur du caoutchouc synthétique</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000416</GUID>
      <Text>Frotz voulait se débarrasser de la récolte complexe des caoutchoucs comme le caoutchouc. Il a découvert une nouvelle façon de fabriquer des caoutchoucs à partir d'autres matériaux de base en travaillant dans des usines chimiques.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Frotz Wogmann, Inventor Of Synthetic Rubber -->
  <!-- START ALL GLASSMAKERS -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000417</GUID>
      <Text>Tous les verriers</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL GLASSMAKERS -->
  <!-- START OTHER KITCHENS -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000418</GUID>
      <Text>Autres cuisines</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END OTHER KITCHENS -->
  <!-- START ALL STEEL INDUSTRY -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000419</GUID>
      <Text>Toutes les industries sidérurgiques</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL STEEL INDUSTRY -->
  <!-- START ALL FILAMENT AND CALBE FACTORIES -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000420</GUID>
      <Text>Toutes les usines de filaments et de câbles</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL FILAMENT AND CALBE FACTORIES  -->
  <!-- START ALL ARCTIC DEPOTS -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000421</GUID>
      <Text>Tous les dépôts de l'Arctique</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL ARCTIC DEPOTS -->
  <!-- START ALL FERTILSER WORKS -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000422</GUID>
      <Text>Toutes les usines d'engrais et de fumier</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL FERTILSER WORKS -->
  <!-- START ALL TEA PRODUCTION  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000423</GUID>
      <Text>Toutes les productions de thé</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL TEA PRODUCTION -->
  <!-- START ALL CHEMICAL PLANTS LACQUER  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000424</GUID>
      <Text>Toutes les usines de produits chimiques Laque</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL CHEMICAL PLANTS LACQUER  -->
  <!-- START ALL VIOLIN PRODUCTION  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000425</GUID>
      <Text>Tous les ateliers de fabrication de violons</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL VIOLIN PRODUCTION  -->
  <!-- START ALL SAILMAKERS  -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000426</GUID>
      <Text>Tous les fabricants de voiles</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL SAILMAKERS -->
  <!-- START ALL FLOUR MILLS -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000427</GUID>
      <Text>Toutes les minoteries</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL FLOURS MILLS -->
  <!-- START ALL TALLOW PROCESSING -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000428</GUID>
      <Text>Tous Traitement du suif</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL TALLOW PROCESSING -->
  <!-- START ALL SLAUGHTERHOUSES -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000429</GUID>
      <Text>Tous les abattoirs</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END ALL SLAUGHTERHOUSES -->
  <!-- START Julie Black, Gas and oil can work together -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000430</GUID>
      <Text>Julie Black, Le gaz et le pétrole peuvent fonctionner ensemble</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000431</GUID>
      <Text>Julie est la sœur de Dennis. Ils ont tous deux grandi avec l'or noir, le pétrole. Mais Julie était plus intéressée par ce qu'elle pouvait trouver dans le sol en dehors du pétrole et a découvert que le pétrole n'était pas la seule ressource qui se cachait sous terre. Outre le pétrole en tant que sous-produit, il y avait des gaz naturels qui pouvaient également être pompés.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END Julie Black, Gas and oil can work together -->
  <!-- START - Olivier Levassier -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000432</GUID>
      <Text>Olivier Levassier, Vous ne passerez pas sans payer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000433</GUID>
      <Text>Olivier est un ancien pirate qui met aujourd'hui ses compétences au service de la gestion du port. Mais pas sans s'assurer de prendre quelque chose pour lui.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END - Olivier Levassier -->
  <!-- START EXPENSIVE THINGS - Rewardpool -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000434</GUID>
      <Text>Des choses chères</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END EXPENSIVE THINGS - Rewardpool -->
  <!-- START - Rudy Scholz -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000435</GUID>
      <Text>Rudy Scholz, Les déchets de la mer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000436</GUID>
      <Text>Rudy s'est installé dans les régions froides de l'Arctique avec l'une des expéditions vers le Nord. Il a perdu l'un de ses meilleurs amis à cause de l'environnement hostile de l'Arctique. Il a été séparé de son ami lors d'une grosse tempête. En recherchant les restes des expéditions perdues, il espère trouver un signe de son ami disparu.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END - Rudy Scholz -->
  <!-- START - Herbert Scholz -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000437</GUID>
      <Text>Herbert Scholz, Les déchets de l'acier</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000438</GUID>
      <Text>Herbert voit des déchets partout dans la production d'acier. Au cours de la production, il est capable de créer des rebuts avec les matériaux restants. Comme son frère et ses sœurs, il travaille dans le secteur de la ferraille.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END - Herbert Scholz -->
  <!-- START - Heidi Scholz -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000439</GUID>
      <Text>Heidi Scholz, rebuts d'armes</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000440</GUID>
      <Text>Comme ses frères et sœurs, Heidi travaille dans le secteur de la ferraille. Contrairement à son frère, elle peut fabriquer des déchets de meilleure qualité.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END - Heidi Scholz -->
  <!-- START - Regina Scholz -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000441</GUID>
      <Text>Regina Scholz, rebuts d'armes perfectionnées</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000442</GUID>
      <Text>Aînée des quatre enfants de la famille Scholz, Regina est la plus avancée en matière de fabrication de ferraille. La ferraille qu'elle produit à partir de la production d'armes avancées est la meilleure que l'on puisse trouver.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END - Regina Scholz -->
  <!-- START - Marie-Antoinette Montagne -->
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000443</GUID>
      <Text>Marie-Antoinette Montagne, les gaz riches</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000444</GUID>
      <Text>Marie-Antoinette est la sœur du père des frères mineurs Montagne. Elle a suivi les fils de son frère dans l'Arctique pour lui promettre de s'occuper d'eux. Outre le gaz arctique, elle a trouvé d'autres gaz riches dans le sol.</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
  <!-- END - Marie-Antoinette Montagne -->
</ModOps>