<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ModOps>
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000002</GUID>
      <Text>William Henry Pilkington, Glass Safety Expert</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000003</GUID>
      <Text>Also known as "Harry". He made his career optimizing the glass making process and specialized in safety glass. No stronger glass can be found.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000004</GUID>
      <Text>Gretl Brown, Mother of the Forests</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000005</GUID>
      <Text>Mother of Ursula and Greta. Wife of Carsten Green. Gretl works together with Ursula in local forests and has a passion for wild berries and making jam. The fruits she uses for her jams are from these very forests and she keeps small colonies of bees to help pollinate the plants and trees.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000006</GUID>
      <Text>Carsten Green, Father of the Arctic Forests</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000007</GUID>
      <Text>Father of Ursula and Greta. Husband of Gretl Brown. Carsten spends most of his time working with Greta in the cold woods of the Arctic. He loves animals and has a particular fondness for huskies. He has a passion for domesticating wild huskies.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000008</GUID>
      <Text>Greta Green, Guardian of the Arctic Forests</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000009</GUID>
      <Text>Following in her father's footsteps, Greta made the Arctic woods her home and her life’s work. Together with Carsten, she spends her days conserving the woods and brewing her own strong drinks to keep warm. She fell in love with a local hunter, Nukilik Takirak.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000010</GUID>
      <Text>Nukilik Takirak, the Strongest Hunter</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000011</GUID>
      <Text>Despite being the most skilled hunter of his tribe, Nukilik has always wanted more from life. Among the few visitors who had come to the Arctic, he met Greta Green and fell in love with her. Greta made his life whole and now they share their love for the forests.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000012</GUID>
      <Text>Brandon Heat, the Perfectionist Charcoal Burner</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000013</GUID>
      <Text>Brandon perfected the art of charcoal burning in the Arctic. He came to the region together with his sister, Jenny. In addition to bolstering the outputs of charcoal kilns, he discovered new ways to extract resin from Arctic conifers.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000014</GUID>
      <Text>Arnakuagsak Takirak, Huntress of the Sea</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000015</GUID>
      <Text>Like her brother, Nukilik, Arnakuagsak learned the skills of Arctic hunting from their parents. Unlike her brother, she prefers hunting on shorelines and in the sea.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000016</GUID>
      <Text>Sir Pryce Pryce-Jones, Warm Clothing for Everyone</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000017</GUID>
      <Text>Sir Pryce is well-known for his entrepreneurial creativity. His bold designs for insulation in clothing are perfect for use in sleeping bags, warm parkas, and fur coats.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000018</GUID>
      <Text>Jenny Heat, It Is Not Just Wood</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000019</GUID>
      <Text>Like her brother, Brandon, Jenny made her home in the Arctic and specializes in processing wood. She loves seeing basic wood developed into functional timber, fit for purpose. The techniques she learned from her brother allow her to create charcoal from sawmill byproducts.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000020</GUID>
      <Text>Aissa Okoro, Smasher of Stews</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000021</GUID>
      <Text>Enbesa was too hot for Aissa. She wanted a colder climate and chose to travel to the Arctic. With her knowledge of seafood stew, she showed the people of the Arctic that Pemmican can also be prepared with fish. Sometimes she even makes seafood stew as a reminder of her life in Enbesa.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000022</GUID>
      <Text>Jean-Claude Montagne, the Perfect Arctic Miner</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000023</GUID>
      <Text>The oldest of the three Mining Brothers. Jean-Claude perfected mining in the Arctic. Gas mines and deep gold mines have no more secrets from him to uncover. He feels responsible for his younger brothers after the death of their parents.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000024</GUID>
      <Text>Jean-François Montagne, the Better Arctic Miner</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000025</GUID>
      <Text>The middle child of the three Mining Brothers. Jean-François adores mining, especially in the brutal conditions of the Arctic. He looks up to his older brother, Jean-Claude, who is exemplary in their craft. Together with his brothers, they form an unmatched triad of mining skill.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000026</GUID>
      <Text>Jean-Marie Montagne, the Sad Arctic Miner</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000027</GUID>
      <Text>The youngest of the three Mining Brothers. Jean-Marie hates cold climates but had no choice other than to follow his older brothers to the Arctic after the death of their parents.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000028</GUID>
      <Text>Amka Etok, Carve to Slide</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000029</GUID>
      <Text>Amka and her brother, Toklo, run their family business. They fashion husky sleds for the people of the Arctic. She has a disdain for the sea and prefers using furs instead of seal skins to craft her sleds.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000030</GUID>
      <Text>Toklo Etok, More Than a Sled</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000031</GUID>
      <Text>Together with his sister, Amka, Toklo perfected the construction of husky sleds, but there is more to him than just knowledge of sleds. Toklo was once given sketches of Steam Carriages by a traveller and was so fascinated with their construction that he learned to build chassis in his spare time.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000032</GUID>
      <Text>Rolf van der Mark, Breeder of Arctic Animals</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000033</GUID>
      <Text>Rolf grew up around animals. In contrast with his brother, Mark, a dog breeder who prides himself on his swift production, Rolf's goal has always been efficiency. They once ran a business with their sisters, Wendy and Judy, but a massive row broke the siblings up and Rolf made his way to the Arctic.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000034</GUID>
      <Text>Jumoke Okoro, the Enbesan Light</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000035</GUID>
      <Text>Jumoke joined his sister, Aissa, on her travels to the Arctic and they quickly fell in love with the endless white landscapes. In Enbesa, Jumoke produced the best-crafted lanterns money could buy. Now, in the Arctic, he works in oil lamp factories and uses his expertise to improve their processes.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000036</GUID>
      <Text>Yuka Saunik, Keep Warm and Light Your Spirit</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000037</GUID>
      <Text>Yuka hates the cold and wants nothing more than to keep her people cozy with warm clothing and bright light. Sister of Inuksuk and Umiaktorvik.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000038</GUID>
      <Text>Umiaktorvik Saunik, Drinks for everyone</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000039</GUID>
      <Text>Umiaktorvik knows how to please people. Whether it is with alcohol or coffee, he makes sure everyone in his company is warm and sated with the perfect drink. Brother of Yuka and Inuksuk.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000040</GUID>
      <Text>Inuksuk Saunik, Keep a Round Belly</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000041</GUID>
      <Text>Inuksuk loves food and he shares that love with his neighbours. He strives to keep the bellies of his people filled and round, even on the coldest of days. Brother of Yuka and Umiaktorvik.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000042</GUID>
      <Text>Philipa Sky, Fast, Faster, Fastest</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000043</GUID>
      <Text>Philipa’s biggest dream as a child was to fly through the clouds. Together with her brother, Phillip, she helped Old Nate learn to navigate airships and made her dream a reality.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000044</GUID>
      <Text>Phillip Sky, Going with the Flow of the Wind</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000045</GUID>
      <Text>As an older brother, Phillip felt responsible for the dreams of his sister, Philipa. Though he planned to become a navy captain, he sacrificed his personal ambitions for Philipa. When he met Old Nate, Phillip saw an opportunity to help the man with his airships and make his sister incredibly happy.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000046</GUID>
      <Text>Colonel Joseph Potts, Expert of Foundries</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000047</GUID>
      <Text>Smelting is a passion of the Potts and as a dutiful member of his family, Colonel Potts took over the family business without question. He modernized it and made safety a top priority in the workplace.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000048</GUID>
      <Text>Alessandro Volta, the Flow of Electricity</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000049</GUID>
      <Text>Alessandro is a groundbreaker in the field of electricity and its transfer. He dedicated his life to sharing his knowledge of power with the world.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000050</GUID>
      <Text>Thomas Alva Edison, Master of Light</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000051</GUID>
      <Text>Thomas designed and perfected the technologies necessary to create a light bulb that could be mass-produced. This invention, together with electricity, brought safer light to the people and created innumerable production and lifestyle advancements.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000052</GUID>
      <Text>Zaire Mto Wa Bluu, Makes the River Flow</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000053</GUID>
      <Text>Zaire loves water. It is the source of all life and a precious resource in Enbesa. After years of research and new insights, Zaire learned how to make water pumps more effective to irrigate larger swaths of land. He is honoured for his contributions to his field.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000054</GUID>
      <Text>Wendy van der Mark, Breeder of Animals</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000055</GUID>
      <Text>Wendy started a breeding business with her brothers, Mark and Rolf, and sister, Judy. Particularly fond of Mark, Wendy was never far from him, considering him her mentor. When Rolf moved to the Arctic and Judy could no longer stand Mark, Wendy stayed by Mark’s side to run their business.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000056</GUID>
      <Text>Judy van der Mark, Sheep and Goat Lover</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000057</GUID>
      <Text>Judy always had a soft spot for sheep and goats. When there were troubles in the family business, she chose to leave. Unlike her brother, Rolf, who moved to the Arctic, she would not leave her sheep and goats for a frigid climate. She sometimes travels to Enbesa to help the local goat farmers.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000058</GUID>
      <Text>Zendaya Chedjou, Meat is Meat</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000059</GUID>
      <Text>From the moment she saw a picture of the Old World, Zendaya had a dream of travelling to this unknown land. When she grew up and had the funds to travel, she took the risk and left everything behind to find her happiness in the Old World. She brought her expertise with her and now works in the slaughterhouses, making delectable new meat products for the people of the region.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000060</GUID>
      <Text>Veronica Castelli, Let It Grow with Less Space</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000061</GUID>
      <Text>Veronica has the same love for crops as her brother, Cosmo. They specialize in Old World crops, but Veronica has learned techniques from New World farmers to produce corn in the Old World, and with fewer fields. She abhors monoculture and always plants trees in her fields, resulting in extra fruit.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000062</GUID>
      <Text>Alisha Al-Zahir, Fewer Fields, More Profit</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000063</GUID>
      <Text>Alisha has her opinions on the ways we grow our crops: she thinks we should use less space to give nature something back. After her travels in Enbesa, she brought her learnings home to the New World. She is a shining example for her brother, Ali.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000064</GUID>
      <Text>Abebe Kanumba, Space Optimization</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000065</GUID>
      <Text>The rain-parched lands of Enbesa are unforgiving to crops. Abebe made it his life’s goal to find better ways to grow crops with less space and using less water. Through his research, he found methods to modify seeds, making it possible to grow plants not previously found in Enbesa.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000066</GUID>
      <Text>Trudy Garnier, Grain is Gold</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000067</GUID>
      <Text>Trudy and her brother, Marie-Antoine, are the perfect baking duo. Trudy processes only the finest grain and her brother uses the resulting flour to bake exceptional bread. Not one to be outdone, Trudy also makes delicious biscuits in her spare time.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000068</GUID>
      <Text>Dennis Black, Pump it Up</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000069</GUID>
      <Text>Dennis’s admiration of oil is so powerful, he would drink it if it were possible. The safety protocols he sets up on his oil refineries are second to none.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000070</GUID>
      <Text>Lucy Roberts, Power to the People</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000071</GUID>
      <Text>Lucy is an unrivalled expert when it comes to power plants. Whether it runs on oil or gas, she has it covered. “Safety first and always” is her motto.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000072</GUID>
      <Text>Macy Parker, No Rendering, No Glory</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000073</GUID>
      <Text>Macy specializes in raising pigs and producing tallow. Her research on pigs and tallow led her to discover unprecedented byproduct production.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000074</GUID>
      <Text>Maurice Dupont, Give the Tractors Some Juice</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000075</GUID>
      <Text>Of the countless technological advancements of this age, Maurice found tractors to be the most fascinating, even as a child. After realizing his goal of owning and operating one of these fantastic machines, he set out to improve and maximize the production of their core need: fuel.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000076</GUID>
      <Text>Polly Davies, Is It Running?</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000077</GUID>
      <Text>Polly eats, sleeps, and breathes machines. As an exemplary engineer, she knows every motor inside and out. If a machine has a motor, Polly has likely dismantled, reassembled, and even improved it.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000078</GUID>
      <Text>Curtis Blink, Make It Shiny</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000079</GUID>
      <Text>Curtis does not like to work with coal and has taken to burning wood instead to melt gold ore. Through his goldsmithing experiments, he succeeded in producing other valuable materials as byproducts.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000080</GUID>
      <Text>Hendrick Harrison, Up and Down</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000081</GUID>
      <Text>Elevators have allowed architecture to reach unprecedented heights. Hendrick was an early adopter of elevator production, but his perspective is that such a marvel should offer occupants a view to the outside. That is why he prefers to use glass instead of wood veneers in his factories.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000082</GUID>
      <Text>Jacques Brun, Baking Chocolate Biscuits</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000083</GUID>
      <Text>Jacques is the primary rival of fellow baker, Marie-Antoine. They both bake with passion and challenge each other in fierce culinary contests. In their last competition, they resorted to fighting and sabotaging one another’s creations. The jury had to intervene and they were both disqualified.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000084</GUID>
      <Text>Henry Mill, Typing 24/7</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000085</GUID>
      <Text>Henry was one of the first engineers to patent the sequential placement of keys on a mechanical transcription machine, a typewriter.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000086</GUID>
      <Text>Zola Kanumba, Mixing the Forest Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000087</GUID>
      <Text>Zola detests monocultural orchards and ensures her fields are always variegated. The collages of magnificent, colourful blossoms offer some of the most amazing views in Old World and New World groves.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000088</GUID>
      <Text>Kofi Adomako, Cigars and Pipes</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000089</GUID>
      <Text>In Enbesa, Kofi was known for his superior clay pipes. He travelled to the New World to learn more about cigars and was so inspired that he left his brother, Adamo, in Enbesa and stayed in the New World.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000090</GUID>
      <Text>Mildred Mitchell, Tailor-Made</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000091</GUID>
      <Text>Mildred is one of the finest knitters in the Old World. Eventually tiring of uninspired, monochromatic Old World designs, he travelled to Enbesa to learn more about the colourful fabrics of that fantastic world. He returned to the Old World, rejuvenated and with so many new ideas.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000092</GUID>
      <Text>Alexander Graham Bell, Calling Home</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000093</GUID>
      <Text>Alexander was one of the investors of the first telephone and undoubtedly made his mark in history.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000094</GUID>
      <Text>Mariana Soto, Weaving Till You Drop</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000095</GUID>
      <Text>Mariana knows every textile and fibre inside and out. For her, weaving is as much an art as it is a profession. She is known for her unique skill of producing paper from textiles.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000096</GUID>
      <Text>Gertrude von Malching, Digging for Gold</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000097</GUID>
      <Text>Mining is a Von Malching family tradition. Like her brothers, Jörg and Fritz, Gertrude is always looking for ways to improve their industry. Recognizing the inefficiencies of gold mining in the New World, she decided to focus her energies on the region and developed remarkable new methods of boosting productivity in local mines. Six is her lucky number.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000098</GUID>
      <Text>Ana Paula Vargas, I Like Sugar and I Cannot Lie</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000099</GUID>
      <Text>For Ana Paula, sugar is worth its weight in gold and she does not care for any recipe without it. Ever the entrepreneur, she is always looking for new ways to expand production and use of sugar. She loves her beer to have a hint of sweetness.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000100</GUID>
      <Text>Juliana Perez, Wool Is the Answer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000101</GUID>
      <Text>Juliana has lost her heart to Enbesa. She travelled there from the New World and not only fell in love with the magnificent continent, but also with a woman, Hibo Ameziane. Together, they started a clothing business. Juliana takes care of the raw materials and Hibo turns the outputs into clothing to keep the people of Enbesa cool and stylish. She uses skills she learned in the New World to turn unprocessed goods into fantastic new fabrics.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000102</GUID>
      <Text>Hibo Ameziane, Stylish Clothing</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000103</GUID>
      <Text>Hibo is one of the best seamstresses and designers from Enbesa. Together with her partner, Juliana Perez, who fell in love with both Enbesa and Hibo, she started a clothing business. Hibo’s designs are comfortable, stylish, and always made with care.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000104</GUID>
      <Text>Ghudan Keita, the Finest Looms</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000105</GUID>
      <Text>The most exquisite tapestries in Enbesa are said to be made by Ghudan. Some claim she has golden fingers, but her secret is the use of only the newest, most precise, and most efficient looms. With leftover linen, she also weaves splendid finery.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000106</GUID>
      <Text>Rua Okoro, with the Tides of the Sea</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000107</GUID>
      <Text>Sister of Aissa and Jumoke, both of whom reside in the Arctic. Rue was left behind in Enbesa when her sisters departed, but she refused to travel to the frigid Arctic. She spends her time in the salt works, optimizing the collection process and extracting new goods from the sea with each rising tide.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000108</GUID>
      <Text>Danen Bamidele, These Boots Are Made for Walking</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000109</GUID>
      <Text>Danen was always intrigued by the versatility and usability of animal products. While working in the dry houses of Enbesa, he witnessed astounding wastefulness. Now, in the dry houses he operates, he encourages the efficient use of all materials and even crafts leather boots on the side.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000110</GUID>
      <Text>Frank Keinehen, He Loves Beer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000111</GUID>
      <Text>Frank is known for his use of unusual ingredients in brewing. He has crafted a wide variety of beers and his latest creation is an ale from Hibiscus petals.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000112</GUID>
      <Text>Fritz von Malching, Mining on the Surface</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000113</GUID>
      <Text>The youngest of the Von Malching siblings. Fritz is claustrophobic and has no love for mountainside mining tunnels. When he learned that workers in Enbesa mine on the surface of rivers, he decided to travel to the continent to attempt to improve this mining method with his expertise.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000114</GUID>
      <Text>Margaret Lee, Clay and Sand</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000115</GUID>
      <Text>Margaret had a fondness for playing in the clay pits when she was a child. Her parents were poor and worked hard to give her an adequate future. As she grew older, her impoverished background stifled her work experience, but her skills with clay were beyond reproach. Her search for a career brought her to the brick dry-houses of Enbesa. She does not resent her situation, owing to her love of clay, and even sculpts ceramics in her spare time.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000116</GUID>
      <Text>Mariette Brun, No Pain, No Grain</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000117</GUID>
      <Text>Mariette is the sister of Jacques Brun, an equally famed baker. Mariette left the Old World for the exotic lands of Enbesa. While there, she quickly realized grain was a perfectly acceptable substitute for teff.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000118</GUID>
      <Text>Ayaan Chedjou, Canned Food Is Better Food</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000119</GUID>
      <Text>When she visited her sister, Zendaya, in the Old World, Ayaan discovered the functional beauty of canned food. When she returned to Enbesa, she used the canning techniques she learned to conserve food and prevent spills in her kitchens.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000120</GUID>
      <Text>Adamo Adomako, Pipes and Cigars</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000121</GUID>
      <Text>Together with his brother, Kofi, Adamo could often be found in the tobacco fields, always on the hunt for the highest quality leaves for his pipes. On their travels to the New World, the brothers learned about cigars. While Kofi decided to remain in the New World, Adamo returned home to Enbesa and brought his extensive knowledge of cigars back with him.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000122</GUID>
      <Text>Elgizouli Nnamani, the Keeper of Golden Bees</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000123</GUID>
      <Text>Elgizouli prefers the company of bees to that of any person. He also adores flowers, which, with bees, is the perfect combination in his line of work.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000124</GUID>
      <Text>Kwame Aku, the Perfect Candles</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000125</GUID>
      <Text>Kwame’s expert hands are said to make the perfect candles. He changed certain basic elements of his process, which results in the extraction of ethanol during candle production. The candles he makes are used by his sister, Makena, to create ornate and beautiful lanterns.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000126</GUID>
      <Text>Makena Aku, Bringer of Light</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000127</GUID>
      <Text>The key to Makena’s skill lies in her love of carving wanza timber, which she uses to craft intricate and sturdy lanterns. The wood she uses in her lanterns is so durable it can withstand the heat of the candles inside. Her brother, Kwame, supplies her with the perfect candles.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000128</GUID>
      <Text>Catherina Hendrika, the First Journalist</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000129</GUID>
      <Text>When typewriters first gained popularity, Catherina saw the opportunity to publish for the university newspaper faster than ever before. She now provides scholars with frequent and insightful press. In her free time, she likes to cuddle with her cat and work in her garden to see her flowers bloom.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000130</GUID>
      <Text>Maya The Cat, Purring to Happiness</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000131</GUID>
      <Text>Nobody has ever seen a more joyful and lovely cat than Maya. She enthrals hotel guests with her warm presence and welcomes each new and returning visitor with a gentle purr.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000132</GUID>
      <Text>Yared Aguta, Shiny, No Colour</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000133</GUID>
      <Text>Yared wanted his ceramics to fetch a higher price. By adding pearls instead of dying the clay, he created new, more valuable pottery that quickly became popular with the people of Enbesa. His processes also allow the production of ceramic jewellery using spare materials.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000134</GUID>
      <Text>Rupert Flanders, Homeschooling</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000135</GUID>
      <Text>Rupert is a staunch believer in homeschooling. “We do not have to go to public schools or universities to learn new things. With the right guidance, we can do that at home.”</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000136</GUID>
      <Text>Jacky Daniels, Drinks for the Rich</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000137</GUID>
      <Text>Jacky learned to appreciate whiskey from an early age. Once she tasted cognac, however, she was interested in little else. Her family was not amused by this change of preference, but her mind was set. Though hugely favouring cognac, Jacky also has a taste for rum and champagne.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000138</GUID>
      <Text>Brian Branch, Basic Wooden Tables</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000139</GUID>
      <Text>Brian and his family make their living through woodwork and have developed countless exceptional wooden products in the Old World. His focus is on simplifying the production of billiard tables. He crafts the tables from normal, solid timber, not fancy cherry wood.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000140</GUID>
      <Text>Brook Branch, Pure Wood, No Shiny Lacquer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000141</GUID>
      <Text>Brook and her family make their living through woodwork and have developed countless exceptional wooden products in the Old World. Her focus is on making violins without toxic lacquer, only pure and beautiful wood. Rather than using lacquer, she crafts her instruments from wood veneers. Brook is also a well-known violinist in the Old World and builds Gramophones to spread her music to the people.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000142</GUID>
      <Text>Brandon Branch, Wooden Toys</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000143</GUID>
      <Text>Brandon and his family make their living through woodwork and have developed countless exceptional wooden products in the Old World. His focus is on wooden toys for children. He never liked the fact that toys were made from celluloid and finished with a toxic lacquer. In his production, he replaced those materials with pure wood to make impressive and natural toys. As it happens, some of his toys can also be used as souvenirs for tourists.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000144</GUID>
      <Text>Irene Braunkopf, Curly, Fresh Hair</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000145</GUID>
      <Text>Irene was working as a hairdresser when she discovered the untapped potential of shampoo production. She began testing new formulas in her home and eventually concocted novel fragrances as byproducts. With these new formulas, she also simplified the production process.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000146</GUID>
      <Text>John Lemon, Sugar-Free Lemonade</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000147</GUID>
      <Text>John does not like sugar and believes it to be an evil against our health. He bottles lemonade with no added sugar, instead using hibiscus petals to reduce tartness and add to the drink’s flavour.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000148</GUID>
      <Text>Britt Branch, Wooden Souvenirs</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000149</GUID>
      <Text>Britt and her family make their living through woodwork and have developed countless exceptional wooden products in the Old World. Her focus is on wooden souvenirs. Her work results in delightful new kinds of souvenirs, made only from the finest wood. Some of these souvenirs are also sold as toys.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000150</GUID>
      <Text>Denise Blink, Lacquer Efficiency</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000151</GUID>
      <Text>Like her brother, Curtis, Denise loves shiny things. The way lacquer makes surfaces glossy gives her the chills. She refined the lacquer production process to produce valuable resources as byproducts.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000152</GUID>
      <Text>Ernesto Vargas, No Sugar, Pure Banana</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000153</GUID>
      <Text>Ernesto is the complete opposite of his sister, Ana Paula. He despises sugar and wants to use it as little as possible in his factories. He manufactures chewing gum with no sugar, replacing the additive with naturally sweet plantains.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000154</GUID>
      <Text>Francesco Plastmasa, Celluloid Efficiency</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000155</GUID>
      <Text>Together with his sister, Francesca, Francesco is always on the hunt for ways to increase production in his plants. They discovered ways churn out more celluloid through more efficient use of camphor wax and ethanol.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000156</GUID>
      <Text>Francesca Plastmasa, Ethanol Overdrive</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000157</GUID>
      <Text>Together with her brother, Francesco, Francesca is always on the hunt for ways to improve production in her plants. With a keen eye for efficiencies in developing ethanol, she learned to ramp up production with no deterioration in quality, even creating valuable byproducts.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000158</GUID>
      <Text>Marco Paulo, Spicing Things Up</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000159</GUID>
      <Text>Marco is a connoisseur of spice and seldom hesitates to turn up the heat in his dishes. “A good meal should always be served with a good hot sauce.”</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000160</GUID>
      <Text>Sister Moppertus, Drinks from the Hacienda</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000161</GUID>
      <Text>Sister Moppertus first devoted her life to God, but upon seeing Brother Hilarius’s amazing work in drink-making, she decided to shift her devotion to the optimization of hacienda breweries. She did not care if this was with God’s consent or not. She loves alcohol.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000162</GUID>
      <Text>Lena Brown, Fertiliser from the Woods</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000163</GUID>
      <Text>Lena is the sister of Gretl Brown and the daughter of Lukas Brown. Like her father, she is invested in the improvement of farmlands through fertiliser. Unlike Lukas, however, she wanted to use more sustainable resources in fertiliser manufacturing and relies on the wonders of the woods to produce it.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000164</GUID>
      <Text>Lukas Brown, Collector of Dung</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000165</GUID>
      <Text>Lukas is the father of Gretl and Lena Brown. Lukas never strays far from his animal farms. He discovered the potential of dung when visiting the New World and, with a bit of “brown magic”, he processes his animals’ dung immediately to fertiliser, ready to use on local fields.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000166</GUID>
      <Text>Valentina de Faro, Chocolate, Coffee, and Biscuits</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000167</GUID>
      <Text>Valentina is the older sister of Fernando de Faro. Fernando learned to make the best coffee from Valentina, who learned the craft from their father, who passed away many years ago. Though they are both exceptional coffee brewers, Valentina’s expertise extends to sweets like chocolate and biscuits.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000168</GUID>
      <Text>Mrs Garrick, Money and Shiny Things Are Not the Answer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000169</GUID>
      <Text>Mrs. Garrick is the sister of Mr. Garrick. She is adamantly against expensive goods and the banking system.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000170</GUID>
      <Text>Georgina Ravenscroft, Inventor of Modern Sand Collecting</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000171</GUID>
      <Text>The glassmaking business was always at the heart of the Ravenscroft industrial empire, but it was solely Georgina who automated and innovated the process of sand collection and saltpetre extraction.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000172</GUID>
      <Text>Lola Mazigh, Persuader of the Sea</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000173</GUID>
      <Text>Lola is the sister of Lalla Mazigh and a relative of Mme. Kahina. When Lola is part of a crew, no captain would dare attack her ship. Her sweet voice can turn even the most bitter enemy into a friend.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000174</GUID>
      <Text>Lou Mazigh, Perfect Trading Routes</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000175</GUID>
      <Text>Lou is the father of Lola and Lalla. Like his daughter, Lola, he is a staunch admirer of the sea and sailing. His optimization of his fleet of ships achieved an unparalleled grade of efficiency for his trade business.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000176</GUID>
      <Text>Flappy, the Best Arctic Friend</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000177</GUID>
      <Text>Flappy is the best friend of Carsten Green, who domesticated Flappy when he was just a pup, abandoned by his mother in the cold woods of the Arctic. Flappy can always be found by Carsten’s side when they wander in the woods. Flappy lifts the spirits of all locals lucky enough to encounter him.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000178</GUID>
      <Text>Flippy, Flippin' Awesome</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000179</GUID>
      <Text>We all know dogs that are just flippin’ awesome. Flippy is one of those dogs. He likes to play with toys that squeak, but as awesome as he is, whenever he hears a squeak, he is so shocked he jumps a meter into the air!</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000180</GUID>
      <Text>Floppy, Herder of Animals</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000181</GUID>
      <Text>Floppy is a fourth generation herding dog. Floppy’s pack has been with the Van der Mark family for generations and has been instrumental in growing their animal farm empire. The Van der Marks hold Floppy and her pack in great regard.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000182</GUID>
      <Text>Kulwa Mto Wa Bluu, Less Damage, More Speed and Cargo</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000183</GUID>
      <Text>Kulwa is the twin sister of Zaire. The siblings share an admiration of water, but Kulwa, favouring exploration, left land and her brother and took to the sea. She has devoted herself to naval service, using her expertise to streamline cargo loading on military ships, reducing slowdown.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000184</GUID>
      <Text>Torpedo Of Doom</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000185</GUID>
      <Text>The ultimate torpedo. No ship can survive its impact.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000186</GUID>
      <Text>Ultra Rapid Canister Shot</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000187</GUID>
      <Text>The ultimate in shrapnel warfare. Bombs flying faster than ever!</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000188</GUID>
      <Text>Sea Mine Of Death</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000189</GUID>
      <Text>Lay these infamous mines under the surface of the water and no ship will pass.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000190</GUID>
      <Text>Auto-Controllable-Pitch Propeller</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000191</GUID>
      <Text>The ultimate propeller technology for steamships.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000195</GUID>
      <Text>Doctor Edward Davy, a Healthy Lifestyle</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000196</GUID>
      <Text>Doctor Davy is a stalwart advocate of a healthy lifestyle. He does his best to encourage patients to use bicycles instead of laze-inducing steam carriages. He leads by example and travels exclusively on his penny farthing. He is also vehemently against smoking and is prepared to lecture any patient on the dangers of cigars.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000197</GUID>
      <Text>Helga Hogarth, Airship Platform Master of Arms</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000198</GUID>
      <Text>Sister of the famous Hogarth the Harbourmaster. Like her brother, she has an active interest in shipping and logistics. She is a leader in efficient airship loading and unloading operations.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000200</GUID>
      <Text>Captain Pirtylo, Scouting from the Sky</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000201</GUID>
      <Text>As a child, Captain Pirtylo lost a close friend, who was kidnapped by pirates. He swore he would find his friend, so even now, he flies around the world, searching.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000202</GUID>
      <Text>Joseph Christians, Talking Sense into People</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000203</GUID>
      <Text>Joseph is the husband of Mad Mary. Despite his love for his wife, he often finds her rash approach to mining unnerving. He balances out Mad Mary’s enthusiastic ideas with shrewd and careful intention, ensuring their work goes according to (his) plan.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000204</GUID>
      <Text>Pirate Captain's Black Sail</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000205</GUID>
      <Text>With this notorious black sail unfurled, a ship’s speed is unmatched.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000206</GUID>
      <Text>Oliver Thorlof, the Happiest Cool Postman</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000207</GUID>
      <Text>A love for communication flows through Oliver’s blood. He follows this passion by being an exceptional postman, even in a land as harsh as the Arctic. No letter goes undelivered without a personal and caring touch, making for delighted recipients.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000208</GUID>
      <Text>Cecce Celeste, Postman Manager</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000209</GUID>
      <Text>Celeste is not your average postwoman: she has learned how to expertly manage post offices in the New World. She expects the best of her postal workers, to deliver each letter with haste and a smile.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000199</GUID>
      <Text>All Old World and New World post offices and post boxes</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000210</GUID>
      <Text>Birdy Bird, Fastest Air Messages</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000211</GUID>
      <Text>A carrier pigeon raised and trained by Postman Oliver. Birdy delivers letters home-to-home with the same precision and diligence as her trainer. Birdy is a delightful surprise to recipients, with her frequent customers even keeping grain on hand as a snack for her while she flies her routes.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000212</GUID>
      <Text>Raveena Bhargava, the Airship Architect</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000213</GUID>
      <Text>Raveena is the sister of Rohit. Like her brother, she devoted her life to ship construction. Her true dream is to be an inventor, so she does her best to make time to pursue the creation of new technologies.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000214</GUID>
      <Text>Ron Rogers, Forger of Fake Mail</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000215</GUID>
      <Text>Ron has been arrested multiple times for forgery, but every time he is released he goes back to his old habits. This time, he has even started a business forging fake mail and selling false stories to the press.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000216</GUID>
      <Text>Brenda Ironbright, the War Must Go On</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000217</GUID>
      <Text>Brenda is the younger sister of Bruno. Both shamelessly found their fortunes in weapon production. Contrary to popular and moral opinion, weapons are always Brenda’s answer to any problem. “Shoot first, ask questions later” is her motto.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000219</GUID>
      <Text>Edsan Orantes, Play Ball!</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000220</GUID>
      <Text>Edsan has been a fan of football for as long as he can remember. As a child it was his game of choice, and as a young man he made a career of it. Now that he is retired, he is an expert in ball production, even manufacturing child-friendly toy balls.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000221</GUID>
      <Text>Jacobus Fussall, Ice Cream for Everyone</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000222</GUID>
      <Text>Jacobus believes the key to the best ice cream is in using the freshest ingredients. He prefers the flavour of coconut ice cream and tries to balance the sugar in his recipes with high-quality flour. His signature recipe is a delectable combination of ice cream and biscuits.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000223</GUID>
      <Text>Koko Flanel, Healthy Perfumes</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000224</GUID>
      <Text>Koko despised the state of the beauty industry and the use of chemicals and alcohol in so many products. She set out to create her own formulas, without needless additives, and prides herself in the manufacturing of skin-friendly goods. Her perfumes are not sprayed, but rubbed on.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000225</GUID>
      <Text>Alfred Lowman, Natural Herbs Cure Everything</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000226</GUID>
      <Text>Alfred believes we can cure all ills with the right herbs and plants found in nature. “By using what is around us, we can create the best medicines and cure all diseases. When in doubt, drink herbal tea!”</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000227</GUID>
      <Text>Holario Javino, Dance, Dance, Baby!</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000228</GUID>
      <Text>Holario is an admirer of samba music and loves to spread joy. For him, dance is a way of life, and he can often be found performing in public, encouraging his audiences to do the same. “We should dance and sing and be happy, not fight to wars, sit in church, or shout in arenas!”</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000229</GUID>
      <Text>General Agnes Mercier, Anarchist Propaganda</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000230</GUID>
      <Text>General Agnes is the sister of Hugo Mercier. Like her brother, she was raised as an anarchist. She believes the cinema is a foolproof way to show the masses how they should live their lives and stay on the "right" path. It is not propaganda if it is true, right?</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000231</GUID>
      <Text>Josephine Grey, Fertiliser Everywhere</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000232</GUID>
      <Text>Josephine is the wife of Lucas Brown. Her relationship with dung and the production of fertiliser is considered strange by some. Despite her eccentricities, she has certainly revolutionized fertiliser production through her unique ethanol-extraction processes.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000233</GUID>
      <Text>Bio-Dung Fertiliser</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000234</GUID>
      <Text>Dung fertiliser with natural additives, proven to increase crop yield. It smells a bit, but who cares?</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000408</GUID>
      <Text>Henrich Morris, Space-Efficient Storage</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000409</GUID>
      <Text>Henrich started a storage business together with his wife, Roberta. They are a fantastic duo, always improving upon their storage efficiencies. Better inventory management, better arrangement, and faster warehouse search protocols. But, of course, efficiency has a price.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000410</GUID>
      <Text>Roberta Dompson, Layered Storage Solutions</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000411</GUID>
      <Text>Roberta runs a storage business with her husband, Henrich. When they travelled to the Arctic on their honeymoon, Roberta was captivated by the beauty of Arctic landscapes. From a professional point of view, she also saw many opportunities to improve goods storage in cold climates, but not without the necessary investments.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000412</GUID>
      <Text>Ferdinand Da Edificio, Monuments Will Rise Everywhere</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000413</GUID>
      <Text>Ferdinand is a building engineer, specializing in some of the largest buildings: monuments. Compared to his colleagues in the field of residential construction, he knowns many more monument-specific efficiencies and safety protocols. The grander the building, the more he likes it.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000415</GUID>
      <Text>Frotz Wogmann, Inventor of Synthetic Rubber</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000416</GUID>
      <Text>Frotz wanted to ease the complex harvesting methods of rubbers like caoutchouc. He discovered advanced new ways of producing rubber using basic inputs of chemical plant manufacturing.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000430</GUID>
      <Text>Julie Black, Gas and Oil Can Work Together</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000431</GUID>
      <Text>Julie is the sister of Dennis, and both grew up surrounded by oil, but Julie was more interested other resources that could be found underground, beyond "black gold". Apart from oil, Julie found, natural gasses can also be collected from wells as a byproduct.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000432</GUID>
      <Text>Olivier Levassier, You Shall Not Pass Without Paying</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000433</GUID>
      <Text>Olivier is a former pirate who now uses his skills of persuasion in managing the harbour. Not without taking a small share for himself, of course.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000434</GUID>
      <Text>Expensive things</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000435</GUID>
      <Text>Rudy Scholz, Scraps from the Sea</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000436</GUID>
      <Text>Rudy moved to the Arctic after an expedition to the North. During a particularly vicious storm, one of Rudy’s colleagues and close friends was separated from their party. By searching for lost expedition scrap, he hopes to find a sign of his missing friend.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000437</GUID>
      <Text>Herbert Scholz, Scraps from Steel</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000438</GUID>
      <Text>Like his brother and sisters, Herbert is in the scrap business. He sees usable scrap everywhere in the production of steel. Using leftover inputs, he can collect functional and valuable materials.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000439</GUID>
      <Text>Heidi Scholz, Scraps from Weapons</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000440</GUID>
      <Text>Like her brothers and sister, Heidi is in the scrap business. With a keener eye than her brother, Herbet, Heidi can find higher quality scrap for reuse.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000441</GUID>
      <Text>Regina Scholz, Scraps from Advanced Weapons</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000442</GUID>
      <Text>As the oldest of the four children of the Scholz family, Regina is the most knowledgeable in scrap collection. The scrap she finds from advanced weapons production is of the highest quality.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000443</GUID>
      <Text>Marie-Antoinette Montagne, Rich Gases</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000444</GUID>
      <Text>Marie-Antoinette is the aunt of the Montagne Mining Brothers. She followed her nephews to the Arctic as a promise to her brother to take care of them. A capable gas and gold miner, she is also highly skilled at finding other rich gases in the ground.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000445</GUID>
      <Text>Premium Copper Distiller</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000446</GUID>
      <Text>Bottle all your drinks in the best premium conditions with this top-notch distiller kettle.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000447</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Potato Sprouts</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000448</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Grain Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000449</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Grape Vines</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000450</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Red Pepper Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000451</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Cane Saplings</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000452</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Tobacco Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000453</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Cotton Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000454</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Cocoa Beans</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000455</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Caoutchouc Saplings</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000456</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Coffee Beans</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000457</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Corn Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000458</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Plantain Saplings</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000459</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Oyster Spawn</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000460</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Hop Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000461</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Animal Bait</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000462</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Nitre Deposits</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000463</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Herb Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000464</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Orchid Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000465</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Linseed Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000466</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Hibiscus Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000467</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Indigo Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000468</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Teff Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000469</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Spices Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000470</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Beehives</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000471</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Lobster Spawn</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000472</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Arctic Forest Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000473</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Arctic Bear Bait</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000474</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Arctic Animal Bait</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000475</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Arctic Caribou Bait</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000476</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Arctic Seal Spawns</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000477</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Arctic Whale Spawns</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000478</GUID>
      <Text>Enbesa Legendary Fertility</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000479</GUID>
      <Text>Arctic Legendary Fertility</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000482</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Vegetable Saplings</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000483</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Hemp Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000484</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Olive Saplings</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000485</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Calamari Spawns</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000486</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Sugar Beet Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000487</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Madder Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000488</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Rice Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000489</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Tea Herb Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000490</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Pepper Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000491</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Mulberry Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000492</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Ume Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000493</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Soy Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000494</GUID>
      <Text>Haye Sanders, Fan Of Letters</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000495</GUID>
      <Text>She loves to use all the Letters of the Alphabet to make the most amazing Art. Her favourite letter is the A. She even made a big marble version of this letter to look at every day.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000496</GUID>
      <Text>Valentino Álvarez, Say Cheese</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000497</GUID>
      <Text>From all the things you can make with cow milk, Valentino chooses all sorts of cheese. Right on the farm he produces the best cheese you can imagine.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000498</GUID>
      <Text>Legendary Avocado Seeds</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000499</GUID>
      <Text>Maurice, Friend Of Everyone</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000500</GUID>
      <Text>Maurice is a 15-year old black cat loved by everyone. Everyone he meets he greets with some lovely purrs. Nobody can ever be harsh against this cutie. He misses a piece of his left ear, nobody knows how this happened.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000502</GUID>
      <Text>Harry Rogers, Loyal Postman</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000503</GUID>
      <Text>In contrast with his brother Ron, Harry is the most loyal postman you have ever seen. Following the rules strictly, never doing something wrong.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000504</GUID>
      <Text>Prior Stamp</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000505</GUID>
      <Text>Send your regional mail more easily.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000506</GUID>
      <Text>Overseas Letter</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000507</GUID>
      <Text>Send nice overseas mail to other regions with special stamps.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1742000508</GUID>
      <Text>All Old World post offices and post boxes</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
</ModOps>
