<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ModOps>
    <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110200</GUID>            <!-- Wadi hot air balloon - Airship -->
            <Text>Wadi hot air balloon</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110201</GUID>            <!-- Wadi hot air balloon - Airship - Description -->
            <Text>A small slow hot air balloon. Perfect if you want to move some smaller amount of goods and time does not matter.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110202</GUID>            <!-- Mara hot air balloon - Airship -->
            <Text>Mara hot air balloon</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110203</GUID>            <!-- Mara hot air balloon - Airship - Description -->
            <Text>A huge sized hot air balloon. Still as slow as the small version, but it can carry a lot of goods.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110204</GUID>            <!-- Cavi hot air balloon - Airship -->
            <Text>Cavi hot air balloon</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110205</GUID>            <!-- Cavi hot air balloon - Airship - Description -->
            <Text>You will only believe when you see one of those. A massive hot air balloon. slow but it can carry a massive amount of goods. It does use helium, so be carefull it does not catch fire or it will light up the sky.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110206</GUID>            <!-- Clipper (Archibald Blake) Balloon Quest - TradeShip -->
            <Text>Clipper (Archibald Blake)</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110207</GUID>            <!-- Joseph-Étienne Gontmolfier - VehicleItem -->
            <Text>Joseph-Étienne Gontmolfier</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110208</GUID>            <!-- Joseph-Étienne Gontmolfier - VehicleItem - Description -->
            <Text>Together with his brother discovered the way of travelling by Hot-air Balloon through the sky. Now focusing on making airships more efficient for trade.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110209</GUID>            <!-- Jacques-Michel Gontmolfier - VehicleItem -->
            <Text>Jacques-Michel Gontmolfier</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110210</GUID>            <!-- Jacques-Michel Gontmolfier - VehicleItem - Description -->
            <Text>Together with his brother discovered the way of travelling by Hot-air Balloon through the sky. Now focusing on making airships more efficient for war.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110211</GUID>            <!-- Common Hot-air Balloon Blueprints - HarborOfficeItem -->
            <Text>Common Hot-air Balloon Blueprints</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110212</GUID>            <!-- Common Hot-air Balloon Blueprints - HarborOfficeItem - Description -->
            <Text>Blueprints to be able to build the most basic Hot-air Balloon.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110213</GUID>            <!-- Rare Hot-air Balloon Blueprints - HarborOfficeItem -->
            <Text>Rare Hot-air Balloon Blueprints</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110214</GUID>            <!-- Rare Hot-air Balloon Blueprints - HarborOfficeItem - Description -->
            <Text>Blueprints to be able to build a more advanced basic Hot-air Balloon.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110215</GUID>            <!-- Legendary Hot-air Balloon Blueprints - HarborOfficeItem -->
            <Text>Legendary Hot-air Balloon Blueprints</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110216</GUID>            <!-- Legendary Hot-air Balloon Blueprints - HarborOfficeItem - Description -->
            <Text>Blueprints to be able to build the gigantic biggest Hot-air Balloon you will have ever seen.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110217</GUID>            <!-- Queens Permission - QuestItem -->
            <Text>Queens Permission</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110218</GUID>            <!-- Flightlogs and sky ship rubble - QuestItem -->
            <Text>Flightlogs and sky ship rubble</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110219</GUID>            <!-- All common specialists - RewardPool -->
            <Text>All common specialists</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110220</GUID>            <!-- All rare and epic airship trade specialists - RewardPool -->
            <Text>All rare and epic airship trade specialists</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110221</GUID>            <!-- Startgoods for our dream in the sky - Quest -->
            <Text>Startgoods for our dream in the sky</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110222</GUID>            <!-- Startgoods for our dream in the sky - BaseNotification -->
            <Text>Congratulations with building your first ship. Reach for the horizon and discover more lands. Have you ever thought about travelling through the sky and not the water? I have been experimenting together with my brother with some new techniques. We think we can make new discoveries! For our first prototype we need some materials. Do you want to help us? We will pay you for the provided goods.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110223</GUID>            <!-- Startgoods for our dream in the sky - NotificationSubtitle -->
            <Text>We need goods to build our first prototype</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110224</GUID>            <!-- Startgoods for our dream in the sky - QuestHints -->
            <Text>As long as we do not have those materials we can not start building the ship. Try to make the corresponding buildings to produce the goods as fast as possible.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110225</GUID>            <!-- Permission from the Queen - Quest -->
            <Text>Permission from the Queen</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110226</GUID>            <!-- Permission from the Queen - BaseNotification -->
            <Text>I heard you are doing research to start conquering the skies. Our Majesty The Queen told me she wants you to stop immediately. Without her permission you can not continue this research. To be able to continue your work you need a written permission signed by The Queen herself. I can provide this to you. Come and get it.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110227</GUID>            <!-- Permission from the Queen - NotificationSubtitle -->
            <Text>Get permission from the Queen to continue your research.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110228</GUID>            <!-- Permission from the Queen - QuestHints -->
            <Text>Archibald can provide you with the needed permission from the Queen to continue your research. Without that the wrath of the queen will come over you.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110229</GUID>            <!-- Lost brother - Quest -->
            <Text>Lost brother</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110230</GUID>            <!-- Lost brother - BaseNotification -->
            <Text>Thank you for doing this for us. The last thing we want is that the Queen shuts us down. Sadly, if you do not mind, I have another request for you. I can not find my brother. I looked everywhere in our workshop and at home. Without him, I can not complete our research. We are not there yet sadly, there are some things we still need to figure out. Can you find my brother?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110231</GUID>            <!-- Lost brother - NotificationSubtitle -->
            <Text>Can you find my brother?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110232</GUID>            <!-- Lost brother - QuestHints -->
            <Text>My brother likes to go for a drink to the pub. Maybe he is there with his comrads?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110233</GUID>            <!-- Extra workforce needed - Quest -->
            <Text>Extra workforce needed</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110234</GUID>            <!-- Extra workforce needed - BaseNotification -->
            <Text>Thank you for bringing my brother back. I would not know what I would do without him! We have made so much progress. But we need some more people to help. Would you want to look for some volontueers that want to help us with the heavy lifting? We will pay them offcourse for all their work.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110235</GUID>            <!-- Extra workforce needed - NotificationSubtitle -->
            <Text>Can you get some extra muscles? They do not have to be from Brussels.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110236</GUID>            <!-- Extra workforce needed - QuestHints -->
            <Text>Look around the streets near the worker houses. There will be people looking for jobs and earning some extra money.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110237</GUID>            <!-- Remember this moment - Quest -->
            <Text>Remember this moment</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110238</GUID>            <!-- Remember this moment - BaseNotification -->
            <Text>We are almost done with our first version. It works based on hot air which rises and lifts the balloon up in the sky! Such an amazing sight. We will start testing as soon as possible and let you know every step of progress. Can you start thinking about a good name for it? We should register this moment by a photo to always remember what we have been through.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110239</GUID>            <!-- Remember this moment - NotificationSubtitle -->
            <Text>Can you make a photo to remember this moment?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110240</GUID>            <!-- Remember this moment - QuestHints -->
            <Text>Make a photo of the sailing shipyard where all those people are working hard.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110241</GUID>            <!-- Save the crew and the flightlogs - Quest -->
            <Text>Save the crew and the flightlogs</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110242</GUID>            <!-- Save the crew and the flightlogs - BaseNotification -->
            <Text>Our first test failed miserably. Our ship in the sky ended up in the ocean. Could you go and look for our flight logs and what remains of our ship? I'm afraid some will probably already have sunk to the bottom of the sea, but I hope we can recover some of it. I hope we can also save the crew and my brother. They were so brave to board the ship, I hope they are ok.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110243</GUID>            <!-- Save the crew and the flightlogs - NotificationSubtitle -->
            <Text>Go look for the crew and the flightlogs in the middle of the ocean.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110244</GUID>            <!-- Save the crew and the flightlogs - QuestHints -->
            <Text>It is not certain what happened but during the flight something went wrong and the ship in the air crashed into the ocean. Pick up the crew and flightlogs from the water.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110245</GUID>            <!-- Gift from the Queen - Quest -->
            <Text>Gift from the Queen</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110246</GUID>            <!-- Gift from the Queen - BaseNotification -->
            <Text>The Queen heard about the accident with the first version of the ship in the air. She is glad to hear that everybody is ok. She send some extra funding to make sure this amazing endavour is going to work out. She hopes ones day she can fly like a bird in one of those ships in the sky, overlooking here queendom.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110247</GUID>            <!-- Gift from the Queen - NotificationSubtitle -->
            <Text>A thank you from the Queen.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110248</GUID>            <!-- Gift from the Queen - QuestHints -->
            <Text>The Queen wants to give you some money to thank you for all your efforts.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110249</GUID>            <!-- Materials to improve the design - Quest -->
            <Text>Materials to improve the design</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110250</GUID>            <!-- Materials to improve the design - BaseNotification -->
            <Text>We analysed the flightlogs and luckily everybody was ok so they could tell us what went wrong. We are ready for the next phase and improve our design. We need extra materials and funds. Can you provide those? We promise it will all be worth it when it is finished!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110251</GUID>            <!-- Materials to improve the design - NotificationSubtitle -->
            <Text>Do you still want to support us and do you still believe in us?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110252</GUID>            <!-- Materials to improve the design - QuestHints -->
            <Text>Provide some additional materials and funding so the research can go on.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110253</GUID>            <!-- Make your first hot air balloon - Quest -->
            <Text>Make your first hot air balloon</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110254</GUID>            <!-- Make your first hot air balloon - BaseNotification -->
            <Text>The Queen is really impatient to see the first hot air balloon. Are you ready to make your first amazing ship in the sky? If you finish it, she is granting you a big amount of money as a prize.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110255</GUID>            <!-- Make your first hot air balloon - NotificationSubtitle -->
            <Text>Your first hot air balloon</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110256</GUID>            <!-- Make your first hot air balloon - QuestHints -->
            <Text>Build your first hot air balloon in the sailing shipyard by using the blueprints you received.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110257</GUID>            <!-- Photo is the amazing first balloon - Quest -->
            <Text>Photo is the amazing first balloon</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110258</GUID>            <!-- Photo is the amazing first balloon - BaseNotification -->
            <Text>What an amazing sight! This is an rare moment. The Queen wants to see this! Make a photograpgh. I'm sure when she sees this it will be a matter of time until she comes here to see it with her own eyes.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110259</GUID>            <!-- Photo is the amazing first balloon - NotificationSubtitle -->
            <Text>A rare photograph of an amazing moment</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110260</GUID>            <!-- Photo is the amazing first balloon - QuestHints -->
            <Text>Photograph the hot air balloon in whatever possible way you want. Maybe with a nice background as the perfect postcard?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110261</GUID>            <!-- First Ship Build - Newspaper -->
            <Text>First Ship Build</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110262</GUID>            <!-- First Ship Build - Newspaper - SpecialEditionHeadline -->
            <Text>First Ship Build!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110263</GUID>            <!-- First Ship Build - Newspaper - SpecialEditionSubline -->
            <Text>An amazing view. The sails weaving in the wind.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110265</GUID>            <!-- Hot Air Balloon Quests - QuestPool -->
            <Text>Hot Air Balloon QuestPool</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1742110266</GUID>            <!-- Hot Air Balloon - Balloon 1 - QuestLine -->
            <Text>Hot Air Balloon - Balloon 1 - QuestLine</Text>
        </Text>
    </ModOp>
</ModOps>